<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-17T15:53:38+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ChelOverboard</title><subtitle>Download Simulation MODs Free Everyday | Join a Community - cheloverboard.com . Welcome to ChelOverboard , Here we specialize on giving Our Users High-Quality MODs that are 100% Working , Follow our Website, Youtube, and Discord Community Today!.# this means to ignore newlines until &quot;baseurl:&quot;</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Syrup and the Magical Sweet (Free-To-Play)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/syrup-and-the-magical-sweet/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Syrup and the Magical Sweet (Free-To-Play)" /><published>2021-01-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-01-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/syrup%20and%20the%20magical%20sweet</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/syrup-and-the-magical-sweet/">&lt;p&gt;it’s about a candy alchemist, syrup, who one day finds a candy golem in her basement workshop. where did she come from?? who the heck made her????? GO FIND OUT!! did i mention there are 10 endings because. that’s right. 10 endings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;content advisory: candy nudity. in some paths she gets eaten. in some paths characters die. there are a few quick screen shakes and flashes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;button&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nomnomnami.itch.io/syrup-and-the-ultimate-sweet/&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">it’s about a candy alchemist, syrup, who one day finds a candy golem in her basement workshop. where did she come from?? who the heck made her????? GO FIND OUT!! did i mention there are 10 endings because. that’s right. 10 endings.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">No Headset No Problems:How to use VRTK Unity Plugin for VR Development without a Headset</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/vrtk-for-vr-testing-without-headset/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Headset No Problems:How to use VRTK Unity Plugin for VR Development without a Headset" /><published>2020-10-22T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/vrtk%20for%20vr%20testing%20without%20headset</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/vrtk-for-vr-testing-without-headset/">&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to start VR development but feel lost because you don’t have a headset? In this tutorial, I’m gonna work you through a technique that makes it possible to build VR content and test them without the need for a headset. The aim of this article is to introduc vrtk plugin through simple explanatiuons and to detail the steps required to set it up on your own development machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we begin, this definition of VRTK aims to give you a broader sense of what it does;
VRTK is a collection of useful, reusable solutions to common problems found when building for virtual reality. VRTK aims to help productivity by speeding up the creation process from prototyping ideas to building complete solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this definition, we can see that this helpul tool can be applied for other use-cases and not just for testing during development process, later in this article, we would breifly cover the main use-cases so you can understand better - what can and can’t be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first section, let’s install vrtk and open a tutorial project in it;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Install and set up VRTK&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Download the zip file of the Unity project that contains the VRTK plugin &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ExtendRealityLtd/VRTK/archive/master.zip&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extract the file to an easily accessible folder on your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open up Unity Hub and select Add, then locate the extracted VRTK folder and select.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Before you can use the tool feature, you have to edit the project settings by setting it up for VR; to do that &lt;b&gt;Go to Edit, Project settings, Player, Under XR Settings - Check VR reality supported&lt;/b&gt; and Under Other settings &lt;b&gt;Make sure that API Compatibility Level is set to .NET 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In the Projects tab, open the folders in this order, Assets,Samples,Farm,Scene - In the Scene folder, Click ExampleScene and open it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the the Game view press play. After about 10 seconds, you can see a farmlike environments and experience it in 360. This process can make development work very easy for you even without a headset. Although, you would need to take a few minutes to learn how the control works, but once u’ve mastered it, this tool can be very effective for testing your virtual reality prototypes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s look at some other features of VRTK that males it such an important VR Dev tool for every developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Features and Other-uses of VRTK&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">Are you looking to start VR development but feel lost because you don’t have a headset? In this tutorial, I’m gonna work you through a technique that makes it possible to build VR content and test them without the need for a headset. The aim of this article is to introduc vrtk plugin through simple explanatiuons and to detail the steps required to set it up on your own development machine.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Best Oculus Hand Tracking Games you can Play right now</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/oculus-hand-tracking-games/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Best Oculus Hand Tracking Games you can Play right now" /><published>2020-10-14T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/oculus%20hand%20tracking%20games</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/oculus-hand-tracking-games/">&lt;p&gt;Are you searching for exciting new vr games to play this month?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are frustrated from buying games only to be left unsatisfied because of poor graphics or unexciting story line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;You’re are not alone&lt;/b&gt;. In truth, That’s been the pain of majority of Gamers. It takes time, a lot of it, to search for quality games that are worth playing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are hundreds of reviews for newly released games by blogs and channels, the thruth is that most of them gets a commission for their time. So, you feel like you are always misled continually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, I wanna stick to the facts in this blog posts. Most of my research are on platforms like Steam, Reddit channels and official websites of these VR developers. Youtube is excluded from my list and that’s because majority of false information concerning Vr games can be found on youtube Channels. That said, &lt;b&gt;Note&lt;/b&gt; that I embed gameplay videos from youtube. This is done only after I have verified the game quality from the other sources mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This list comprises newly released Vr titles and those that have not gained enormous popularity yet. I chose to excluded the best VR games like Half-life, Beat Saber etc, because chances are you have heard of these titles, played them, or are yet to. That said, let jump right into the top Vr Games with Hand-Tracking enabled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;10+ Best Hand-Tracking Vr Games On Oculus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Phasmophobia&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/arKjeSLA3n0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a phychological ghost multiplayer Vr game unlike any ghost vr game you have played till now. It has great graphics which are very realistic. 
&lt;br /&gt;
In this game, you can play with your freinds, how fun is that?. The goal is to hunt down ghosts with fancy gadgets and provide evidence of paranomical existence

It is a still a new game with first release on September 24 but it has a huge community and fan-base which are mostly positive in reviews.

The Game supports all the major VR headsets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/739630/Phasmophobia/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;The Room VR: A Dark Matter&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iySB6jnYwYE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game falls in-between mystery and explorer. One outstanding feature is it's graphics. Explore cryptic locations that have been designed with such realism. It also comes with a very good story: You are a detective sent out by The British Institute of Archaeology to investigate the sudden disappearance of an esteemed Egyptologist. 
&lt;br /&gt;
If you are interested in investigation and puzzle experiences like me, then you would love this game.
&lt;br /&gt;
Another aspect of the game worth mentioning is the smaller fan-base it has. This can be said to be the result of the &quot;genre&quot; of this adventure which I assume most people aren't interested in. But if you are, then you must buy this game. It's wonderful
&lt;br /&gt;
One review from Edge magazinge completes my thought about this game:
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&quot;The Room has never been short of atmosphere, but in VR it’s more enveloping than ever. The quality of the craftsmanship is hard to deny, and what follows is as thrilling a VR experience we’ve had outside City 17, with a finale that blends Lovecraft and Spielberg.”
8/10 – EDGE Magazine&quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

The Game supports all the major VR headsets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1104380/The_Room_VR_A_Dark_Matter/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Panoptic&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vNuZ5kg2DC0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is kind of an action game(because you fight in it. But not exactly full-time action). It also has some fantasy atmosphere in it. It's a local multiplayer game(you can only play with friends close by). You can play as Giant Overseer or Tiny Challenger and whatever role you pick, you get to win if you defeat you opponent by tracking them down or excaping through the crowds in both cases. 
&lt;br /&gt;
It graphics lays around being mysterious,unsettling  and scenic rather than robustness like can be found in Half-Life. If you love Vr games with stelth and intensity then you should absolutely check this out, Like NOW!.
&lt;br /&gt;
I haven't personally tried it out, yet. But from the reviews of a game just out on October 8, something fantastic must be going on it.

The Game supports all the major VR headsets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1104380/The_Room_VR_A_Dark_Matter/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Karnage Chronicles&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/POAGlE7P5HM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Karnage Chronicals is a mystical RPG Action Vr game. I have to give it to them for the graphis, they are legit realistic. You can feel the kind of atmosphere portrayed by just watching a preview of it. So in Karnage, the story is that a the world is ruled by magic and you are tasked with finding a cosmic force and cryptic. It's clearly a magical adventure but the game doesn't let in on that on the title page.
&lt;br /&gt;
After watching the preview, the game is awesome. It has humor and funny characters, i think a tiny goblin?
&lt;br /&gt;
As such, it has a good community following and positive reviews. It's not a game I would play, I'm not really into action in ancient worlds. If all the elements and features of karnage can be replicated in an action game but with guns, that's my ideal type.
&lt;br /&gt;
After watching the preview, what do you think? would you be playing karnage soon? can't make a decision? Let me help; If you like magic, ugly creatures and quests that involves splashing around the gore of creatures! Hmm? Ok, I think you get the point now
&lt;br /&gt;
Karnage Chronicles supports all the major VR headsets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/611160/Karnage_Chronicles/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Britannic: Patroness of the Mediterranean&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KNgxcXdv8j0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game is an adventure in the Britannic, sister of the in famous Titanic ship and how it sunk after striking a mine during the First World War. 
&lt;br /&gt;
So in case you didn't figure yet, it more like an educational and learning experience, but that's not all. It has detailed information about the Britannic, it's architecture and contributions to the World War.
&lt;br /&gt;
Although, it's just an education vr adventure, I was surprised by the amount of Positive ratings which tells that this game has a lot more to offer than just what we see in the preview.
&lt;br /&gt;
The Game supports all the major VR headsets exempting Windows Mixed Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1259560/Britannic_Patroness_of_the_Mediterranean/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;WAR DUST - 32 vs 32 Battles&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/arfqaR0GvK0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Vr game is action-packed with breathtaking action film, full of explosions and dynamic tactics.
Wardust is a massive multiplayer VR game where upto 64 players can feature in a match.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&quot;With 64 fighters on the battlefield, War Dust will take you into the largest online battles that have ever been made in VR. Everyone has a role to play on the battlefield: one single man, at the right place at the right time, can make a decisive difference. Get ready to be this difference, to dare, to fight, and defeat your enemies.&quot; ---War Dust Steam&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
While the graphics are not robust, don't let that full you. In reality, the battleground for war is never an amazing sight.
&lt;br /&gt;
If you have the competitive and strategic mindset, War dust is the only VR game currently that can give you as much satisfaction you can get from action-strategy. So don't miss the chance to compete!
&lt;br /&gt;
Wardust supports all the major VR headsets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/957790/WAR_DUST__32_vs_32_Battles/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Tales Of Glory&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/D6jRgABS_is&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a medieval vr fantasy game set around the world of battle between towns. The special thing about this game is it's ability to engage in melee attacks with realistic physics.
&lt;br /&gt;
One more reason I love this game, is that altghough it's a battle ship game, you can experience other environments like the bar and club.
&lt;br /&gt;
In your missions, you don;t just fight, you can ride an horse, run, shoot an arrow, in fact almost everything that a real-life battle brings with it.
&lt;br /&gt;
Already Interested? You should. If you're looking for an exciting and adventurous Vr title with many activities, this game has it all - plus it is packed with 30 hours of game time exploring medieval worlds and protecting your lands. Shoot!

Still having some doubt- read this review by UploadVR
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;“Mount &amp;amp; Blade is an extremely popular and successful series of medieval simulation games in which you raise an army, conquer kingdoms, and engage in epic, intense battles with dozens of troops around you. From sieges to horseback rampages, it’s got it all. Tales of Glory is basically that, but in VR.”
UPLOAD VR&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

Tales of Glory supports all the major VR headsets exempting Windows Mixed Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/636970/Tales_Of_Glory/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;ZomDay&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OPASrEAXWsY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ZomDay is an outstanding Zombie Vr game. As zombie crisis broke out around the world,you will play one of the warrior of Special Event Action Team to fight against the zombies all over the world.ZomDay is a fast pace VR shooting game contains multi-player mod,exciting Boss fight,character perk and hardcore weapon system.
&lt;br /&gt;
Relentless zombies will launch waves of attacks, the monsters will cooperate with each other, the battle will be harder and harder, you can use the drop Buff to temporarily improve the combat capability, or deal with the enemies by means of terrain. 
&lt;br /&gt;
Yes, cheer up! Fight alongside your teammate! You can join an open game at any time! You will feel quite different under on-line mode: you can make an attack formation together with your teammate as a defense for the incoming monsters, help your teammate such as buy bullets and weapons, and give your teammate your weapon

&lt;br /&gt;

ZomDay supports all the major VR headsets exempting Windows Mixed Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/681390/ZomDay/?snr=1_7_7_230_150_5&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Boiling Steel&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MZQy_tzyQWg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are one of many who set off in search of a better life in the distant bastion of scientific progress. Your goal is a colony planet, free from bureaucratic, religious and other radical restrictions.
&lt;br /&gt;
Here they research and freely use industrial teleportation, transfer of consciousness and other technologies prohibited in the inhabited worlds. Factories, power plants, mines and residential complexes of the planet are fully automated. All the dirty and hard work is done by robotic shells controlled by the operator’s mind. It is a high-tech paradise. But here, something went wrong.
&lt;br /&gt;
As soon as you wake up from a long sleep in a capsule of hibernation, you fall into circulation. Radical fanatics are here too. A virus was launched into information networks that turned robots into aggressive death machines. The paradise planet plunged into the chaos of war. The inhabitants of the colony took the seats of the operators of robotic shells and sent their army of robots into battle. Joint efforts have borne fruit.
&lt;br /&gt;

Boiling Steel supports all the major VR headsets exempting Windows Mixed Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1016860/Boiling_Steel/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Rocking Legend&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/arfqaR0GvK0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rocking Legend is a musical game where you take the part of a virtual guitarrist immersed in beautiful and dynamic environments.
&lt;br /&gt;
Choose from a selection of guitars and original rock/metal inspired instrumental songs and compete on the global leaderboards the way you like, with your preferred control scheme and a selection of gameplay modifiers.
You can also play with custom songs (integrated editor and support for external .chart or .mid maps made with external tools).
&lt;br /&gt;

Boiling Steel supports all the major VR headsets exempting Windows Mixed Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1260800/Rocking_Legend/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Valve Index, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings us to the end of the list. Among them, the best Oculus Hand-tracking VR games to play in 2020. This list is ranked based on positive reviews, graphics, game time length, physics and a few other designs. Spoiler, most games in the list have a price tag on them and if you are like me, you are probably thinking “aren’t there any top but &lt;b&gt;free&lt;/b&gt; Vr games around”?. Lucky for us, some developers open their games for everyone to play for free. This list should reveal these top titles to you that you can play right now &lt;a href=&quot;https://cheloverboard.netlify.app/free-vr-games-2020/&quot;&gt;Best Free VR Games for 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">Are you searching for exciting new vr games to play this month?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Things you must absolutely know before starting VR Development in 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/things-to-know-for-vr-development/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Things you must absolutely know before starting VR Development in 2020" /><published>2020-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/things%20to%20know%20for%20vr%20development</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/things-to-know-for-vr-development/">&lt;p&gt;Do you want to become a full-fledged virtual reality developer and make money from your games?. I know you do. Here’s one thing, starting off on the wrong foot can make it very tough for you to attain that level in the expected amount of time before you lose the passion you once had. Here’s why:
&lt;!-- Statistics --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the process of gathering any new skill there are two very important things you should keep in mind: Decision &amp;amp; Action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can’t make prompt decision, the action side of things diminishes significantly. And that’s not very good because actions makes you achieve goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog post I will cover and explain all the necessary areas you should know before getting in vr development for whatever purpose you might have(video games, education, movies, medicine, automobiles).Please Note that, more attention is focused on video games development in vr. Let’s begin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the steps guiding us through this article:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gentle Introduction to VR Development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10 Essentials for VR Dev (Main Content)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10 Great tools for VR Development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Summary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;What is virtual reality development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Developers, storytellers, artists, beginners, etc. all have an opportunity to build immersive experiences using an exciting new technology that literally pushes the bounds of content creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VR content development is similar to 3D game development in that it the spatial design of a large, immersive 3D worlds that the player/user will traverse on her own. But in truth, it is not similar to 3D game development, there is a wide range of differences between the two like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Immersion: The users are placed in a virtual space, cut from the real world on a sensory level. VR headsets allow this by occupying their whole field of vision, while headphones achieve the same results with sounds, thus fully immersing the users in another world.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Positioning: How is the world positioned relative to the user(player)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Double Lens: The worlds must be viewed from a double lens headset, how to provision for this&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Interaction: To feel real, a simulated environment should include virtual elements we can interact with: picking up an item, swinging a sword to kill a goblin, breaking a mug, pushing the ignition button of plane in a flight simulator, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sensory feedback/Tracking: Vr headsets track the position of the users within a given space so that the computer renders the changes of positions. Users moving their heads or bodies will be given the illusion that they are moving in the virtual world.
In short, a vr world has to meet a few or all the features above for it to be considered immersive.
Keeping that in mind, let’s look at how &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; can kickstart career in Virtual reality for whatever your purpose might be.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;10 Essentials to know before starting VR Development&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4&gt;Begin your Technical training&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So you want to start creating VR worlds and certainly you have some ideas on where to start or you don’t have at all. Thankfully, there is a small circle of resources available for you to choose from so here it’s easier to make a decision. The two main softwares/game engines we have that can accomplish your goals are unity and unreal engine. As a beginner it is recommended to start with unity for these benefits:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Unity has a very simple learning curve. You can start making simple games and intercations in a little as a week if you put in enough time, believe me.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Unity is free for all to use until you start earning a large sum of money which by then you would have no problems in showing appreciation by paying up.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Unity has wide and growing support for other purpose aside from video games like movie production, 3D animation, education, medicine and space. As you can see, there is something for everyone.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;There is &lt;b&gt;a lot&lt;/b&gt; of resources you can use to learn and improve your vr development skill. Unity is dedicated to helping beginners be successful in thier chosen course.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I expect that you have a decision to make unity your development home because it would favour you greatly. About the resources i mentioned, these would help you get started:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity3d.com/learn/tutorials/topics/virtual-reality/getting-started-vr-development&quot;&gt;Unity Learn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity3d.com/learn/tutorials/topics/virtual-reality/getting-started-vr-development&quot;&gt;Unity Youtube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity.com/solutions/automotive-transportation-manufacturing&quot;&gt;Film, animation and cinematics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity.com/solutions/automotive-transportation-manufacturing&quot;&gt;Automotive, Transportation &amp;amp; Manufacturing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity.com/solutions/architecture-engineering-construction&quot;&gt;Architecture, Engineering &amp;amp; Construction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unity.com/solutions/edtech&quot;&gt;Build quality learning apps, games and simulations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Using this resources, you can start to work with unity to realize your dream of building VR world in any industry.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h3 id=&quot;choose-your-focus-technical-or-graphical&quot;&gt;Choose your Focus: Technical or Graphical&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Just like in 3D game development, VR general purpose development also demands skillful focus on two main areas: Technical(Building the environment and making it interactive with codes) and Graphical(designing the environment with artistic software,assets). This tells you that it is not recommended to be the programmer and the graphics designer at the same time: It just wont work for you. I used to think that if I put in a lot time, I could achieve everything alone but in truth, for you to become a pro in VR development you would have to put in so much time and efforts which is not guaranteed if you are doing two things at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Now let’s say you decide to focus your resources in coding , you might be asking how you can acquire assets to use for building your environment and scenes. Why this mnight have been a big concern a few years back for indie createors, it isn’t anymore there are lots of ways you can get graphics to complete your projects. Follow the steps below where I would guide you through the process:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h4 id=&quot;for-technical-and-programming-focused&quot;&gt;For Technical and Programming focused&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As someone focused on developing vr applications on unity engine alone, you want a simple way to get the assets/models of your choice to use in prototype and production level versions. I have compiled a list of the best places to get models, most are free others cost a few dollars.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://assetstore.unity.com/&quot;&gt;Unity Asset Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sketchfab.com/&quot;&gt;Sketchfab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://poly.google.com/&quot;&gt;Google Poly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cgtrader.com/&quot;&gt;CGTrader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.turbosquid.com/&quot;&gt;Turbosquid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h4 id=&quot;for-graphical-and-design-focused&quot;&gt;For Graphical and Design focused&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you are graphics inclined and want to develop for vr, focusing on your skills would bring great benefits in time. The market for virtual reality desginers is expected to grow by 10% by 2025 according to statista. This is because 60^ of people involved in  3d games and VR development are software devs and programmers. But, as you may have thought you also require the skills of a programmer in whatever projects you might take up, I sourced around for the best way to go about this:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Consider searching on some freelance websites dedicated for VR Development&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Get involved in the Unity/VR Reddit groups. many people have found partners and went on to complete projects together. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Unity3D/&quot;&gt;Reddit Unity3D&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/virtualreality/&quot;&gt;Reddit virtualreality&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;In the first case though, you would need to spend some cash for hiring a developer you can team up with. I recommend selling your graphics skills either on some frelance websites you can find or generally any of the listed 3D models store above.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h3 id=&quot;determine-your-target-platform&quot;&gt;Determine your Target Platform&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This means that you should identify the platform or device your VR applications would work on. Is it a specific OS like Android, IOS, Windows or General like mobile devices against PC. Also, ofc we have the newer Standalone devices like Oculus Quest, Go, Rift and HTC Vive which runs on AndroidOS and Steam VR respectively. As a beginner, it is necessary that your applications has support for mobile devices because it’s easier to market it to consumers. Also as a business/company creating VR experiences to market a new product to your customers, it’s more realistic to develop for mobile devices has greater audience.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h3 id=&quot;test-your-work-with-the-right-hardware&quot;&gt;Test your work with the right hardware&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Every VR Developer needs to have a test unit to see how the application works and what bugs need to be fixed while still in development mode. Depending on the kind of app your are building, your VR gear and system would vary.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;If you want to target casual users of VR, develop for Google Daydream or GearVR, you would need to have a similar VR Headset for your dev process This would ensure that you have a working prototype similar to how you want your users to interact with your app with no flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;And if you want to target premium VR users, develop for Oculus Rift or HTC Vive, you would need to make the adjustments for that.
Once you’ve determined your target platform and associated hardware/headset, consider any computing requirements. For Rift and Vive, you’ll likely need to invest in a PC gaming computer that contains a solid graphics card.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h3 id=&quot;consider-the-system-reqirements&quot;&gt;Consider the System Reqirements&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Before installing your preferred software in this case Unity Engine, be sure that your computer meets the necessary system requirements for development process. This would help you before-hand evaluate your system specifications and make any necessary adjustments before you begin.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Below is the required system specs for unity VR Development:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;windows&quot;&gt;Windows&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;OS: Windows 7 SP1+, 8, 10, 64-bit versions only; macOS 10.12+&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GPU: Graphics card with DX10 (shader model 4.0) capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Processor: 1.1 GHz Processor&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Memory: 4 GB RAM&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Storage: Upto 10GB Free Space allocated for Unity Dev&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these you know know what’s in store and can make tweak your system if it does not already meet the required specs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there you have it, 5 things to consider before starting VR development. This can take you just a day to figure out or in some cases, weeks. It all depends on how prepared you have been till now i.e learning the ropes. That said, I think some tools will be greatly helpful for you in your vr journey whatever your propose might be. Take a look at them below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;top-5-vr-software-development-tools&quot;&gt;Top 5 VR Software Development tools&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;unity&quot;&gt;Unity&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Unity is famous for game development, however, it helps you to build VR solutions for many other sectors too. E.g., you can create VR solutions for automotive, transportation, manufacturing, media &amp;amp; entertainment, engineering, construction, etc. with Unity.
You can get a valuable set of tools when you use Unity, e.g.:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A powerful editor to create VR assets;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Artist and designer tools;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CAD tools;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Collaboration tools.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Read more about them in “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/virtualreality/&quot;&gt;Unity 2019: performance by default, high-fidelity real-time graphics, and artist tools&lt;/a&gt;”. Unity works with all popular VR platforms like Oculus, Sony, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;amazon-sumerian&quot;&gt;Amazon Sumerian&lt;/h4&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sumerian/&quot;&gt;Amazon Sumerian&lt;/a&gt; is the VR engine from AWS, and you don’t need 3D graphics or VR programming skills to use it. Sumerian works with all popular VR platforms like Oculus Go, Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, HTC Vive Pro, Google Daydream, and Lenovo Mirage, moreover, it works with Android and iOS mobile devices too.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Amazon Sumerian supports various VR use cases like employee education, training simulation, field services productivity, retail &amp;amp; sales, and virtual concierge. It has powerful features, e.g.:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Sumerian editor;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Sumerian hosts;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Asset management;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;An ability to script the logic in the scenes you create.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Read more about these features in “&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sumerian/features/&quot;&gt;Amazon Sumerian features&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You can access extensive learning resources that will help you to use Sumerian, and you can read “&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sumerian/getting-started/&quot;&gt;Getting started with Amazon Sumerian&lt;/a&gt;” for this. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sumerian/faqs/&quot;&gt;Amazon Sumerian FAQ page&lt;/a&gt; has plenty of valuable information that’s useful for any virtual reality developer. Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sumerian/pricing/&quot;&gt;Amazon Sumerian pricing page&lt;/a&gt; for its pricing plans.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;google-vr-for-everyone&quot;&gt;Google VR for Everyone&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Google, the technology giant offers a wide range of VR development tools, and you can use them to create immersive VR experience for your stakeholders. You can access these tools on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/vr/&quot;&gt;Google VR developer portal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You can use these tools to develop VR apps for multiple platforms, e.g., Unity, Unreal, Android, iOS, and web. To access the guides to develop VR apps for each of these platforms, first navigate to “&lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/vr/develop/&quot;&gt;Choose your development environment&lt;/a&gt;” on the Google VR developer portal.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Google VR developer platform has software development kits (SDKs) for all VR platforms it supports, e.g., Unity, Android, iOS, etc. You can navigate to the download page on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/vr/download/&quot;&gt;Google VR developer portal to access them. You can read “&lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/vr/reference/&quot;&gt;Google VR API reference&lt;/a&gt;” to understand the Google VR APIs, which covers all SDKs that the Google VR development platform offers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;blender&quot;&gt;Blender&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Blender is an open-source 3D creation suite, and it’s free. At the time of writing, Blender 2.80 is its latest release. The Blender Foundation, an independent organization for public benefit governs the development of Blender.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Blender offers the following features and capabilities:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You can create your 3D pipeline with modeling, rigging, animation, simulation, rendering, composing, and motion tracking.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Blender supports video editing and game creation.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;If you have an experienced VR developer in your team, then he/she can use its API for Python scripting to customize the application. This allows you to create specialized tools.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blender.org/download/&quot;&gt;download Blender&lt;/a&gt; for using it on a Windows, Mac, or Linux computer. Visit the documentation page on the Blender website to read its manuals, moreover, you can also access &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blender.org/support/tutorials/&quot;&gt;its tutorials&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h4 id=&quot;oculus-medium&quot;&gt;Oculus Medium&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Oculus, the well-known provider of VR platforms like Oculus Rift S, Oculus Quest, and Oculus Go also offers powerful VR development software, named &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oculus.com/medium/?locale=en_US&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a comprehensive tool, which allows you to create 3D assets.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You can sculpt, model, and paint the VR assets you create. Even if you are a beginner, with Oculus Medium you can quickly create an immersive environment.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/c/OculusMedium&quot;&gt;Oculus Medium YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; has many useful videos, and you can view them to get more information on this tool.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 5 Virtual Reality development tools I have described above can help, however, developing a VR solution can be complex. With this guidelines and steps in VR development, you should be able to start your journey for what purpose you have. This is a lengthy article and as such, you might have questions circling your mind. The comments section is provided just for that reason, and don’t hesitate to leave me a question. Thanks Chel_&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">Do you want to become a full-fledged virtual reality developer and make money from your games?. I know you do. Here’s one thing, starting off on the wrong foot can make it very tough for you to attain that level in the expected amount of time before you lose the passion you once had. Here’s why: On the process of gathering any new skill there are two very important things you should keep in mind: Decision &amp;amp; Action.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Before buying a VR headset in 2020 here are the Essential List of things to consider</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-vr-headsets-oculus-rift-htc-vive-samsung-gear/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Before buying a VR headset in 2020 here are the Essential List of things to consider" /><published>2020-09-27T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best%20vr%20headsets%20oculus%20rift%20htc%20vive%20samsung%20gear</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-vr-headsets-oculus-rift-htc-vive-samsung-gear/">&lt;p&gt;VR is the new drill for gamers, with it comes much hassel about what is the trend and how to keep up with it. To be honest it can leave you significantly unsatisfied with the choices you make . That’s what the ongoing excitement around VR is meant to create among gamers and developers. Should it be this way? - Probably Yes, if at all a thing is exciting enough people should be ready to chop their heads off for it (virtually so). Is this healthy for you , Mentally and Financially so - Certainly not XD. What were you expecting me to say. My aim for this article is to provide a comprehensive guide that would direct your thoughts into making the best choice for your “Cause”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the steps guiding us through this article:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you need an Oculus Rift S?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The essentials to consider before making a choice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to go about making a satisfying VR headset choice for your CAUSE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly you might have had conflicting opinions and felt unsatisfaction with choices you may have made concerning VR products till now, but that’s only normal. As humans, when we are excited about a new trend, we tend to feel every choice we made was the wrong one, we are always looking for the perfect one. In truth, this has been the same with every trend-setting product released till date - Iphone X, Windows Updates, Branded Clothes etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Do you need an Oculus Rift S&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you need an Oculus Rift S vr headset now? - Chances are you don’t need one. As is the case, gamers feels like they surely do, but this in truth is not always necessary or essential to their needs. I consider myself a gamer, not just that - I’m passionate about experiencing VR gaming. But I can’t see myself buying an Oculus Rift S with mine or my parent’s money for some important reasons, to find out if you need an oculus rift s, consider these questions below and answer them according to your own situation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many hours do you spend on VR gaming every week? Less than 10 hours and you probably do not&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Can you afford the cost of an Oculus Rift S with you own personal income?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What do you hope to achieve with an Oculus Rift: Intense game competition, Youtube Let’s play videos, VR- game Development
Let’s consider the following:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For Intense Gaming and Youtube Let’s play videos, it’s possible in every respect to opt for a more affordable headset that would work just as well as gaming on an Oculus headset.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For vr development, it’s not advised to limit your testing headset to an Oculus or better still, as a beginner, Oculus supported games are NOT the best starting point for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conclusion - No matter what use case you want a VR headset for if your budget does not adequately allow for it, an Oculus Rift S is not the best option to consider as other more affordable brands can achieve your goals for you without hassels. That being said, there still exist a lot of options to consider which can prove confusing andd intangible for a noob to comtemplate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next few sections, I would give you a working cheat sheet to help you contemplate and secure the best decision for your personal unique situatiuon. Read on!!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Features/Essentials of a VR headset&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before we start, I want to assure you that while surface-discussing the features of a VR headset, I choose to leave the technical details alone on Wikipedia because I assume you fall into the category of Gamer/VR Dev and sincerely just want a straight-forward honest discussion on these terms. Now let’s begin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some essential key point features of VR headset that Brands look to include in their products are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Quality: The quality of a VR headset refers to it’s rendering power. i.e how fast it is able to play 3D graphics every second. In computing language this is called fps or frames per seconds. One small detail to note: because a vr headset has two viewing angle(providing separate images for each eye), it has to render 2X the graphics of a game whereas a regular PC or gaming device renders just once. As a result, this leads to low quality in some experiences or frame-skipping. Vr headsets also come with gyroscopes, accelerometer and magnetometers, the power of these head-tracking sensors dirctly determines the quality of the headset. Now you know some of the details, it’s necessary to check the capacity of a headset so you know what to expect before-hand. Today as technology keeps advancing, VR headsets comapnies are finding it less difficult to equip their product with working quality systems.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Control: Some VR Headset comes with controllers equipped, this is a device that enables hand-tracking so the player’s movement can be simulated in the Vr world. Most games today require a player’s movement for interaction within the game, so this is a very important feature. An addition to controllers &lt;i&gt;Haptic feedback&lt;/i&gt; is the sense of touch designed to provide information to the end user, is already built into a number of existing virtual reality controllers&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Comfort: Most VR Brands live up comfortably to this particular feature, but certainly when considering low priced headsets you have to consider the comfortability it comes with. In short,&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Does the headset feel comfortable to wear for long use&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Can the strap - if it comes with one, be adjusted or removed for cleaning&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Does it feel itchy or heavy to put on
These are some questions to consider when checking the comfort that comes with a VR headset.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How to go about making a satisfying VR headset choice for your CAUSE.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here I would highlight some necessary steps you can take to choose the best vr headset for you current situation and needs.
There are essentially, three categories of VR headset when grouped based on price:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;low-priced headsets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;medium-priced headsets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;high-cost headsets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all cases and situations, people use products &amp;amp; items differently. Some use it more, other less. Defining what your proirities are in using a vr headset would already tell you which group you belong to.
To make the selection process easier for you, I would highlight some popular use cases of a vr headset today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Popular Use-Cases of a VR headset&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gaming: By far, the most popular use case of a vr headset is for playing Vr games. You have to ask yourself two very important question: How much time do you spend on gaming?, Do you spend money to purchase high-quality vr games?. After arriving at the answers to these questions, make a decision on what kind of vr headset you need:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Usually if you spend less than 5 hrs a week playing vr games &amp;amp; you don't spend money buying vr games, I recommend going for a medium-priced headsets. Below I will give you a variety of options to choose from&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;On the other hand, go for a highpriced headset if you spend substancial time and money on vr games, if you use a headset professionally like a for youtube channel &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;VR Development: With that mentioned, a group of people dedicated to developing for vr exists and if you fall under that group, I have got you covered. Likewise, two main sub-groups exixst:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Do you develop vr games for sale are you an intermediate vr developer, if so a medium quality headset should work fine for testing prototype and scenes according to the quality of your games.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Are you a beginner or hobbyist to vr games development. You might be an indie game dev but are not yet making money from your games. If you fall into anyone of these, a low-priced headset would do the job for you and also saved you irrelevant expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that’s sorted, by now you should have a decision in mind based on which cases are similar to your needs. Below you can review the headsets of your choice before making a purchase decision and start living your dream of owning a virtual reality headset for whatever purpose; gaming, entertainment, development etc.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">VR is the new drill for gamers, with it comes much hassel about what is the trend and how to keep up with it. To be honest it can leave you significantly unsatisfied with the choices you make . That’s what the ongoing excitement around VR is meant to create among gamers and developers. Should it be this way? - Probably Yes, if at all a thing is exciting enough people should be ready to chop their heads off for it (virtually so). Is this healthy for you , Mentally and Financially so - Certainly not XD. What were you expecting me to say. My aim for this article is to provide a comprehensive guide that would direct your thoughts into making the best choice for your “Cause”.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">15+ Quality and Affordable VR Headsets that you can Purchase right Now (Almost Just like the Oculus Go)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/vr-quality-headset-not-oculus-go-or-gear-vr/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="15+ Quality and Affordable VR Headsets that you can Purchase right Now (Almost Just like the Oculus Go)" /><published>2020-09-21T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/vr%20quality%20headset%20not%20oculus%20go%20or%20gear%20vr</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/vr-quality-headset-not-oculus-go-or-gear-vr/">&lt;p&gt;“Virtual reality headsets are only as good as the experiences they offer”. If that statement reads true, why do the gaming community debate tirelesssly over the Oculus Rift and HTC Vive HMDs. Starting today this shouldn’t be the case for you, there are dozens of VR headsets looking to offer you great quality and experience without first cashing out on you. Wanna find out?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Main targets of this article&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What should you get from a VR headset&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quality Headsets to Buy that are not Oculus, HTC, Valve Index or PSVR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s much ongoing debate in the gaming community about which VR headset is the best among others. There are thousands of reviews by people looking to change your opinion on which headset to buy, although they do this with a good cause in mind. In reality, this only strenthens the arguments people have and causes much confusion for people like you, and earlier on - me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This should not at all be the case. Most importantly, you should not alllow yourself to be dragged into this rave because it’s expected to continue on for a long time as Facebook(Oculus) and (HTC Vive) release new versions of their headset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Virtual reality headsets are only as good as the experiences they offer”. I got this statement from PCMag, a reputable website that writes on VR. Certainly, that statement reads true, so why do we all bother with all the arguments and indecisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve played a few VR games till now, geared with the HTC Vive, one thing stands true - if the quality of the game isn’t fantastic, you get the same quality regardless of what headset you have on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say all this without even considering the enormous price tag on them. It’s just pointless considering you can derive the same satisfaction regardless of the headset you use, In fact “quality largely depends on the game”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Who is this Article mainly for&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article is for three categories of people:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You are yet to buy a headset, confused between Oculus, HTC, Valve Index since that seems to be what everyone talks about but “you want something cheaper that fits your budget”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You have sufficient budget to purcahse a top-priced headset but just like me you are conservative and would consider all options where you can get a decent quality headset that works just like Oculus etc.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You are an avid gamer, you want something similar to Oculus &amp;amp; co, you are stubborn to not bring your expectation down a bit, also you don’t want to spend so much on a vr headset. Trust me on this one, this post is also for you.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I introduce some fantastic affordable headsets to you and also to prove the validity and relevance of this article, I want to go through the main components of a VR headset thatmuch people weigh before making a decision to buy or not to. The point of this is to streamline/filter my list to products that meet the required components to a very decent level. I do not hope to delve into the technicalities of these properties, I’m just gonna be using a language gamers understand best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Features of a VR Headset&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Quality: The quality of a VR headset refers to it’s rendering power. i.e how fast it is able to play 3D graphics every second. In computing language this is called fps or frames per seconds. One small detail to note: because a vr headset has two viewing angle(providing separate images for each eye), it has to render 2X the graphics of a game whereas a regular PC or gaming device renders just once. As a result, this leads to low quality in some experiences or frame-skipping. Vr headsets also come with gyroscopes, accelerometer and magnetometers, the power of these head-tracking sensors dirctly determines the quality of the headset. Now you know some of the details, it’s necessary to check the capacity of a headset so you know what to expect before-hand. Today as technology keeps advancing, VR headsets comapnies are finding it less difficult to equip their product with working quality systems.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Control: Some VR Headset comes with controllers equipped, this is a device that enables hand-tracking so the player’s movement can be simulated in the Vr world. Most games today require a player’s movement for interaction within the game, so this is a very important feature. An addition to controllers &lt;i&gt;Haptic feedback&lt;/i&gt; is the sense of touch designed to provide information to the end user, is already built into a number of existing virtual reality controllers&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two are the basic features of a vr headset, some headsets don’t come with all the sensors and systems mentioned but I make it my business to bring you the best headsets that are affordable and effecient.
We come now to the main content of this post:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;20+ Quality and Affordable Headsets to Buy 2020&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VR Headset for Nintendo Switch, OIVO 3D VR (Virtual Reality) Glasses, Labo Goggles Headset for Nintendo Switch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VR Headset for Nintendo Switch&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61SSZLacZxL._AC_SL1050_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Upgraded Version: Special virtual reality vr glasses for Nintendo switch, would be a big surprise as gift for your friends and family or yourself, this is the upgraded version.(More suitable experience and people with prescription glasses can wear this VR too.).NOTE: Please take out the Joy-Con would be light weight to use, 15~36mm, may not fit for huge nose. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Say Goodbye To Carboard Materials: Made of EVA and Oxford materials, super light weight and durable, no worry that your VR glass get mildew in wet weather, includes adjustable headstrap and more thick materials to touch your face, no need to grip the switch console near your head. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Watch and Play in VR: HD optimization takes you special experience to watch Youtube and play Super Smash Bros. &amp;amp; Zelda &amp;amp; Super Mario Odyssey etc. (VR games may be updated in succession), Full range with the joysticks and the buttons are covered fully, easy to use when playing action games (I.e. smash bros.) &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/OIVO-Headset-Nintendo-Virtual-Reality/dp/B07TBPLQJS/ref=sr_1_13?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-13&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;BNEXT VR Headset Compatible with iPhone &amp;amp; Android Phone - Universal Virtual Reality Goggles - Play Your Best Mobile Games 360 Movies with Soft &amp;amp; Comfortable New 3D VR Glasses - Red - w/Eye Protection&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;BNEXT VR Headset Compatible with iPhone &amp;amp; Android Phone&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/7187vvRAA3L._AC_SL1500_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ ADVANCED VR GAMING TECHNOLOGY - Gaming and watching movies with virtual reality headsets work best when your eyes properly align with the screen box. That’s why our VR headset offers FD and OD adjustments (wide FOV) to expand the viewing angle and perfectly match focal distance and unilateral myopic alignment for reduced distortion &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ COMFORTABLE, EXTENDED WEAR DESIGN – Once you start gaming and watching VR movies with 3D goggles, you’re never going to want to take it off. That’s why we offer a comfort-fit experience with a fully adjustable head strap, eyesight protection system, and a soft nose piece to reduce pressure. Can also support drones that require a phone VR headset &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ VR SMARTPHONE COMPATIBILITY: Smartphones with a gyro sensor (almost all models) and with a 4&quot;-6.3” screen. Examples: VR goggles are compatible with models X, XR, XS, 8, 8 plus, 9, 9 plus, 10, 7, 7 plus, 6, 6s, 6s plus, 6 plus, 6, 5, 5 plus, 5c, 5s, SE, etc. Also compatible with Samsung Android Galaxy s8, s7, j3, s7 edge, s6, s6 edge, note5, a8+, note 3, note 4, note 5, note 7, note 8, note 9, s5 s6, s7, s8, s8 plus, s9, s9 plus, s10, s10 plus, one plus, Box VR etc. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Headset-iPhone-Android-Phone-Comfortable/dp/B07Q3NCJYP/ref=sr_1_10?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600648837&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-10&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VeeR Falcon VR Headset with Controller, Eye Protection Virtual Reality Goggles to Comfortable Watch 360 Movies for Android, Samsung, Huawei and iPhone (only for 4.7-6.2inch)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VeeR Falcon VR Headset with Controller, Eye Protection Virtual Reality Goggles&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61HuOp1ugIL._AC_SL1200_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ VeeR Falcon VR Headset is designed and developed for comfortable use. VeeR VR Video App updates Every Month. You will have a lasting experience on your new Falcon headset with VeeR VR Content App. Search 'VeeR' on play store or app store, discover a huge VR Content library and without pay &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Built in HiFi active noise canceling around-ear headphones from Falcon Headset give you crisp, powerful sound and quiet that helps you enjoy your VR movies, games and music better. Feel like watching a huge screen of 1050 inch in a distance of 3 meter, visual angle between 100 and 110 degree, which contributes to immersive visual experience with high definition photos &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Built-in microphone and the 3.5mm headphone jack is easy to answer calls directly by headset. The unique bi-focus adjustments (FD/IPD) allow you to expand the viewing angle and depth for each eye and it fit perfect for everybody especially those with short-sighted &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VeeR-Headset-Controller-Universal-Comfortable/dp/B07G37CLJ5/ref=sr_1_25?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-25&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VR WEAR Virtual Reality Headset, Goggles Gear, Google - 3D VR Glasses VR 3D Box for Any Phone (iPhone 6/7/8/Plus/X &amp;amp; S6/S7/S8/S9/Plus/Note and All Android Smartphone) with 4.5-6.5&quot; Screen&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VR WEAR Virtual Reality Headset, Goggles Gear, Google - 3D VR Glasses&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71S-gH7dwcL._AC_SL1500_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ HIGH-END DESIGN The headset has a semi-transparent lid for camera – augmented reality (AR) movie provided &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ SUPPORTS ALL 4.5-6.5 SMARTPHONES: VR WEAR virtual reality headset is compatible with such smartphones as iPhone and all other PHONES within 4.5-6.5&quot; equipped with a gyroscope &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ INDIVIDUALLY ADJUSTABLE DOUBLE LENS: VR WEAR virtual reality viewer has a comfortable lens adjustment in 4 directions for each eye separately - adjusting the focus and IPD (interpupillary distance) &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ COMFORTABLE WEARING: VR glasses face cushion is made of soft leather. Soft and elastic head strap relieves the pressure on the nose and face. The VR goggles are very light weight, you can get a better immersive virtual reality experience) &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VR-WEAR-Virtual-Reality-Headset/dp/B07PVNVQ5L/ref=sr_1_26?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-26&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VR Headset Virtual Reality Headset 3D Glasses with 120°FOV, Anti-Blue-Light Lenses, Stereo Headset, for All Smartphones with Length Below 6.3 inch Such as iPhone &amp;amp; Samsung HTC HP LG etc (BR)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VR Headset Virtual Reality Headset 3D Glasses with 120°FOV&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61CoGeu%2BmsL._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Fits for All iOS, Android, Windows Smartphones with Length Below 6.3 inch (Screen size between 4.0&quot; to 6.5&quot;), such as Samsung Galaxy Note 5/4/3/2, S9 S9+ Plus S8 Plus S8 S7 Edge/Galaxy S6 S5 S4 J8 J7 J6 J3 J2 A6; Apple iPhone SE 11 11 PRO XR XS Max XS XR 10 X 8 8 plus 7 7S 7 Plus 6s 6 Plus 5c 5s; LG V30 V20 V5 G6 ZONE 4 V30+ Aristo Moto Z2 E4 G5 Huawei Nexus 6P 6 5X Nokia 6 8 2 3310 HTC 10 U11 626S M9 530, etc &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ There is an integrated 3.5MM audio jack connects with your mobile, if your mobile has no 3.5mm audio socket, try to find an adaptor with one side is 3.5mm audio socket to enjoy the crystal VR sound &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ VR EMPIRE headset is the only one with Anti-blue light lenses in the amazon market; our eyes will be protected from harmful blue light emitted from all mobile screens. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Friendly recommend several VR apps or content websites: Incell VR, Jauntvr.com; 360heros.com; LittleStar.com; Discoveryvr.com; Wavrp.com;  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VR-Headset-Virtual-Anti-Blue-Light-Smartphones/dp/B08BJDCPW6/ref=sr_1_23?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-23&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VR Headset with Bluetooth Headphones, Eye Protected HD Virtual Reality Headset,VR Glasses for iPhone and Android Phone Within 4.7-6.2Screen&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VR Headset with Bluetooth Headphones, Eye Protected HD Virtual Reality Headset&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61Z8WJIytSL._AC_SL1200_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Eye Protected Anti-blue Light HD Lenses - Eye-protected lenses with unparalleled clarity make VR movies a visual experience comparable to world-renowned IMAX. Adjustable headphones will cover your ears right and bring good sound.It will always make sure you have the best seat in your private theatre wherever you really are &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Adjustable Pupil and Adjustable separately Focus Distance - You can simply adjust the position of the lens through turning the button on the top of the 3D VR GLASSES to get clearest view without your own glasses (even for consumers with myopia under 600°, hyperopia under 300° or astigmatic under 100°). &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Wide Compatibility - Share the vr headset with the whole family! Don't worry about the Phone's sound output interface is lighting or 3.5mm jack or else,The Build-in Bluetooth can easy to connect to your phone. And It supports smartphones with 4.5-6.2 inches screen, such as iPhone X 8 7 plus/6s/6/6 plus, Samsung s8/s8 Plus/s7/s7 Edge/s6/s6 Edge Note8/5/4/3, LG g6 g5 g4 g3 v20, and Daydream phones like Google Pixel/Pixel XL/Pixel 2/Pixel 2 XL, Samsung s8/s8 plus, Moto Z/Z Force, Huawei Mate 9 Pro &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VR-Bluetooth-Protected-Smartphones-4-5-6-0in/dp/B07G74XL46/ref=sr_1_22?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-22&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VR Headset for iPhone &amp;amp; Android Phone,3D VR Glasses for TV,Movies &amp;amp; Video Games,VR Headset with Remote Controller,Virtual Reality Headset for iPhone/Android Phone Compatible 4.7-6 inch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VR Headset for iPhone &amp;amp; Android Phone,3D VR Glasses for TV,Movies &amp;amp; Video Games&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61WwNb553SL._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ 2 lenses are designed independently, pupil distance and object distance adjustment are available for myopic population. Our model supports naked eye viewing with myopia below 0-600 degrees and direct viewing with myopic glasses. After wearing it, please adjust the left (right) pupil distance to suit yourself. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ headset for iPhone/Android phone Compatible 4.7-6 inch,3D glasses can turn mobile phones into cinemas/3D game halls. The product does not need to be recharged, 1. Download VR app 2.Search for the 3D video（left and right format） you want to watch in the vr app. 3.put cell phone into the VR glasses，Put on VR glasses and adjust pupil distance.and then you can watch it.With Bluetooth remote controller, the effect is better. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VR-Headset-Android-Controller-Compatible/dp/B07Y68297Y/ref=sr_1_21?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-21&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Merge VR Headset - Augmented and Virtual Reality Headset, Take Virtual Field Trips, Watch Educational 360 Degree VR Videos, STEM Tool for Classroom and Home, Works with iPhone and Android (Moon Grey)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;Merge VR Headset - Augmented and Virtual Reality Headset&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41B%2ByEWroUL._AC_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Award-winning STEM learning, the Merge Headset has been featured in Consumer Reports, named by CNN as Best VR Headset for Big Kids and Tweens, and Winner of the Academic's Choice Award &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Compatible with the Merge Cube for mixed reality experiences (not required). &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Go Anywhere with the Merge Headset - find apps and experiences at Merge Miniverse online; explore the solar system, walk with dinosaurs, take virtual field trips and more; works with Google Expeditions &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/MERGE-AR-Headset-Augmented-Experiences/dp/B06XT7QBCV/ref=sr_1_20?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-20&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;WapSter Vr Headset, Sneba White Virtual Reality, Headset VR Glasses for 3D Video Movies Games for Apple iPhone 11, Samsung Huwei HTC More Smartphones.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;WapSter Vr Headset, Sneba White Virtual Reality, Headset VR Glasses for 3D Video Movies Games&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61Elni9PujL._AC_SL1500_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ EASY FD OD ADJUSTMENT: Gaming and watching movies in VR boxes works best when your eyes properly align with the screen box. That’s why our VR Glasses offers FD and OD adjustments wide FOV to expand the viewing angle and perfectly match focal distance and unilateral myopic alignment for reduced distortion. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ REVOLUTIONARY OPTICAL SYSTEM: It completely eliminates vertigo. Virtual reality headset is suitable for everyone, even including those who have myopia. Pupil settings for the best 3D experience. 3D vr headset has innovative design, comfortable super lighter weight, wearable and adjustable straps for flexible wear. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ ENJOY APPS GAMES LIKE NEVER BEFORE: You can download over 1000 of vr apps from Apple Store and Google Play - for FREE. You can also enjoy fully interactive 3D videos from YouTube or dedicated VR websites. Immersing into fascinating 360° Videos Games have never been easier. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/WapSter-Headset-Virtual-Reality-Smartphones/dp/B081NQVPMB/ref=sr_1_18?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-18&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VIFE, Virtual Reality Headset,3D VR Glasses for Mobile Games and Video &amp;amp; Movie,Compatible 3.5-6 inch iPhone/Android Phone,Including iPhone,Samsung, LG,etc (Gold - No Remote)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VIFE, Virtual Reality Headset,3D VR Glasses&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51p6Wq3UXVL._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ VIFE is a VR headset that transforms your smartphone into a portable VR device. Want to fly in the sky? Want to see the Dragon? Let's enjoy the Virtual Reality entertainment and see the reality in a different way! &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ VIFE has a suction pad for holding the mobile that can avoid the mobile falling down when you moving. Two-way focal control (focal distance &amp;amp; pupil distance) ensures different mobile can focus cleanly. Two-way airflow (Top &amp;amp; Bottom) ensures cool air is directed to the mobile. T-shaped top strap ensures a snug fit. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ ENJOY APPS GAMES LIKE NEVER BEFORE: You can download over 1000 of vr apps from Apple Store and Google Play - for FREE. You can also enjoy fully interactive 3D videos from YouTube or dedicated VR websites. Immersing into fascinating 360° Videos Games have never been easier. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/VIFE-Bluetooth-Controller-Compatible-Including/dp/B07V6HLWB2/ref=sr_1_30?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-30&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;VIOTEK Spectre Folding Virtual Reality VR Headset Phone Accessory - Lightweight Glasses with Collapsible Case for Samsung Apple iPhone LG HTC Motorola Nokia Google Pixel and More!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;VIOTEK Spectre Folding Virtual Reality VR Headset Phone Accessory&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51jw9Xv5EOL._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ OPEN FACE DESIGN - Allows the phone's camera to open a portal to the world of augmented reality for these VR Glasses. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ CAPACITIVE TOUCH – This button allows you to fully immerse yourself into Google cardboard and iPhone VR games. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ FOR ALL VISION TYPES – Adjust the sliders to focus picture and get the best viewing experience for your vision. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ 3D TECHNOLOGY - The VIOTEK Virtual Reality Goggles can play 3D Movies and Games on 4.5-6 inch iPhone and Android devices. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Spectre-Folding-Virtual-Reality-Accessory/dp/B01N1QZD60/ref=sr_1_33?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-33&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;BOBOVR Z4 Virtual Reality Headset, 3D Glasses 120°FOV Adjustable Focal Length Stereo Headphone VR for 4.0-6.0 inch Smartphone&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;BOBOVR Z4 Virtual Reality Headset, 3D Glasses 120°FOV Adjustable&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51Bjt6kkG-L._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ BOBOVR is made of high quality ABS, PMMA and PET. The environmental spherical resin lens can lower down the distortion to the minimum when magnifying images, so you will not feel dizzy even with wearing it for a long time. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Adjustable T-shape straps and elastic support structure help decrease the pressure around your forehead and eyes when wearing it, so you will feel much more comfortable when watching movies or playing 3D games. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Built-in stretchable 3.5mm jack earphones, with soft memory foam for noise canceling provide stereo sound. Package includes a ergonomic remote controller that realizes multiple functions such as play video, control volume, Flip E-book page. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Wide compatibility: fits most smartphones of screen size 4&quot; to 6&quot; including Samsung Galaxy Note 10/9/8/5/4/3/2, S10e S10+ S10 S9 S9+ Plus S8 Plus S8 S7 Edge/Galaxy S6 S5 S4 J8 J7 J6 J3 J2 A6 ; Apple iPhone iPhone 11/11 Pro/11 Pro MAX XS Max XS XR 10 X 8 8 plus 7 7S 7 Plus 6s 6 Plus 5c 5s; LG V30 V20 V5 G6 ZONE 4 V30+ Aristo Moto Z2 E4 G5 Huawei Nexus 6P 6 5X Nokia 6 8 2 3310 HTC 10 U11 626S M9 530 etc. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/BOBOVR-Virtual-Adjustable-Headphone-Smartphone/dp/B08BJLSJCK/ref=sr_1_36?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-36&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Virtual Reality Goggles for iPhone &amp;amp; Android Phones | 3D Virtual Glasses | AR/VR Headset Perfect Work with Max Size Smartphones | Eye-Safe Adjustable HD Quality Lenses (Premium)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;AR/VR Headset Perfect Work with Max Size Smartphones&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71dDFSQZQaL._AC_SL1500_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ COMFORTABLE: digib vr goggles are very light, do not hurt your nose and protect your eyes. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ PERFECT VIEWING ANGLE AND IMAGE CLARITY due to high quality HD VR lenses. &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ WORKS WITH MOST SMARTPHONES: Our VR viewer is compatible even with XXL screen phones up to 6.3&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Wide compatibility: fits most smartphones of screen size 4&quot; to 6&quot; including Samsung Galaxy Note 10/9/8/5/4/3/2, S10e S10+ S10 S9 S9+ Plus S8 Plus S8 S7 Edge/Galaxy S6 S5 S4 J8 J7 J6 J3 J2 A6 ; Apple iPhone iPhone 11/11 Pro/11 Pro MAX XS Max XS XR 10 X 8 8 plus 7 7S 7 Plus 6s 6 Plus 5c 5s; LG V30 V20 V5 G6 ZONE 4 V30+ Aristo Moto Z2 E4 G5 Huawei Nexus 6P 6 5X Nokia 6 8 2 3310 HTC 10 U11 626S M9 530 etc. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/digib-Virtual-Smartphones-Eye-Safe-Adjustable/dp/B07JC8BMSD/ref=sr_1_41?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-41&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like I promised, I would provide a solution for you if you fall under the third category of people “&lt;b&gt;You are an avid gamer, you want something similar to Oculus Go, Gear Vr, Daydream &amp;amp; co, you are stubborn to not bring your expectation down a bit, also you don’t want to spend so much on a vr headset. Trust me on this one, this post is also for you.&lt;/b&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suggestions below should help you find what you are searching for. By following the links, you are led to Amazon where you can purchse a “used” Vr headset for a considerable lesser amount. No need to bother, I have verified the sources to be legit and you should experience zero problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Brand New Oculus Go and Daydream Alternatives&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Samsung Gear VR Virtual Reality Headset&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;Samsung Gear VR Virtual Reality Headset&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/611bTWaanrL._AC_SL1000_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Light weight so you can play and watch more comfortably &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Improved fit, including room for most eyeglasses and improved padding for extra comfort and durability &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Compatible with: Samsung Galaxy S7, S7 edge,Note5,S6 edge+,S6,S6 edge &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ wide field of view, precise head-tracking and low latency brings reality to the virtual, Be transported to amazing new worlds, in games, video and images, Thousands of 360 degree panoramic photos &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Samsung-Virtual-Reality-Headset-Lightweight/dp/B01L96KA4Y/ref=sr_1_48?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-48&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Oculus Go Standalone Virtual Reality Headset - 32GB&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;Oculus Go Standalone Virtual Reality Headset - 32GB&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; src=&quot;https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/610iXon9LfL._SL1300_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	✅ Personal Viewing: The littlest, big screen. Crystal clear optics and state-of-the-art 3D graphics make your headset feel more like a personal theater &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Viewing with Friends: Watch with friends. Meet up in VR with friends and fans from around the world to catch live sports, concerts, or just your favorite TV show &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Controller: Effortless control. Whether it's navigating to your favorite shows or to a far-off land, the intuitive controller makes getting there a cinch &lt;br /&gt;
	✅ Portable &amp;amp; Easy to use: Ready when you are. Experience portable, all-in-one VR. That means no PC, phone, wires or hassles &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Oculus-Standalone-Virtual-Reality-Headset-pc/dp/B076CWS8C6/ref=sr_1_19?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=vr+headsets&amp;amp;qid=1600699763&amp;amp;s=electronics&amp;amp;sr=1-19&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s it, the best list of quality virtual reality headsets that are cheap and affordable. I hope this you make a decision after reading this post, and I also learnt that you don’t necessarily need a brand new Oculus Go for you to start gaming in VR. There are a lot of slightly used that work just as well for a significant decrease inprice. I think you should take the chance. With this article, you can find a headset suitable to your style and budget and that’s what is most important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kudos to VR brands for making thier headset very economical so thw world of VR is easily accessible to millions and hopefully keeps growing. Thanks for going on this journey with me, leave a reply and tell me about the choice you made after reading this, I would be pleased to hear your story. Chel_&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">“Virtual reality headsets are only as good as the experiences they offer”. If that statement reads true, why do the gaming community debate tirelesssly over the Oculus Rift and HTC Vive HMDs. Starting today this shouldn’t be the case for you, there are dozens of VR headsets looking to offer you great quality and experience without first cashing out on you. Wanna find out?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">5 Technologies that would change VR Gaming in 2021 (With Exciting New Introductions)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tech-that-would-change-vr-2021/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5 Technologies that would change VR Gaming in 2021 (With Exciting New Introductions)" /><published>2020-09-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tech%20that%20would%20change%20vr%202021</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tech-that-would-change-vr-2021/">&lt;p&gt;In reality, virtual reality can still be referred to as an emerging technology. Surely it has not still gotten to it’s peak or highest point as we have predicted. That considered, nobody can take away the excitement surrounding gaming in vr. With all the ongoing rave about vr games today, it is a wonder how the vr gaming industry would react with the introduction of the latest technologies surrounding Virtual Reality like Haptic Feedback and . If you haven’t been current in the going-ons in virtual realiuty tech and breakthroughs, this article would show you the top technologies that would change virtual reality games giving them unparralled realism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you don’t get bored fast, I decided to leave out the extra explanation on the how’s,when’s, and why’s of these technologies. If you are anything like me, you want to perhaps understand the surface of these tech and what you can expect them to bring to the virtual reality games of the future(as early as 2021).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First I would give simple introductions to the technologies in question, next a simple example from my imagination how they can be utilized in vr games starting 2021. Let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;5 Technology that would Transform VR Gaming&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">In reality, virtual reality can still be referred to as an emerging technology. Surely it has not still gotten to it’s peak or highest point as we have predicted. That considered, nobody can take away the excitement surrounding gaming in vr. With all the ongoing rave about vr games today, it is a wonder how the vr gaming industry would react with the introduction of the latest technologies surrounding Virtual Reality like Haptic Feedback and . If you haven’t been current in the going-ons in virtual realiuty tech and breakthroughs, this article would show you the top technologies that would change virtual reality games giving them unparralled realism.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Best VR Games for September - Newly Realeased, Coming Soon top picks</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/top-10-vrgames-september/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Best VR Games for September - Newly Realeased, Coming Soon top picks" /><published>2020-09-15T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/top%2010%20vrgames%20september</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/top-10-vrgames-september/">&lt;p&gt;If you are an avid gamer playing the latest vr games every other day, this article is compiled just for you. In this article, we filter through the many game titles available on steam, HTC Vive, oculus quest etc to provide you with the top picks for septemer 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this article is to reduce the time you spend rowsing through lists to make a decision yourself. If after going through the list and you fell like we missed a virtual reality game that deserves a space in the top best, don’t hesitate to mention this in the comments section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are writing this post currently in nthe mid of septemer, so take note that a few would include coming-soon vr games filtered based on highest anticipation, early-releases, pre sale and game developers. Now onto the list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;10+ Best VR Game Releases in September 2020&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;DEEMO -Reborn-&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_3NO5lwQzpQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Background Story&lt;/b&gt;
A girl who fell from the skies and lost her past; Deemo who plays the piano all alone in the world of the treehouse; an accidental encounter between the two. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Features:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
  A Classic Reborn: Centered around an ancient castle and a mysterious tree that grows when melody is in the air, control the little girl who has fallen from the sky and help her find her way home. &lt;br /&gt;
  Investigation Reborn: Unravel riddles and mysteries hidden in the castle. Find sheet music that falls from the heavens, unlock new places, and discover the truth. &lt;br /&gt;
  Rhythm Reborn: Play your heart out on the piano and make the mysterious tree grow. Unveil new parts of the story and look forward to the day that the girl can return to her heart-warming home.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1282210/DEEMO_Reborn/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Starblazer&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0KTPjG25xvY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience the thrill, fast pace, and funk of Starblazer®. Clash with friends and join the many curious-minded commanders that have found a VR strategy game that everyone can play. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;EXPANSIVE UNIVERSE.&lt;/b&gt; The glitz and sheen of Saffron Stadium. The tranquil creeks of Blossom. The fiery sun of Icarus. The neon vibes of Incomplex. The lavish lights of Melody. The many varieties of maps and arenas keep gameplay unique and interesting. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;UNIQUE SHIPS, BUILD COUNTLESS FLEETS.&lt;/b&gt; Craft the perfect fleet, choose your favorite ships, and design unique combinations. With 8 different types of ships, no fleet is ever the same. Simple “rock-paper-scissors” gameplay makes this an easy strategy game for everyone to pick up and play, while leaving lots of options for players looking for a challenge. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;DEFEAT ENEMY FLEETS, FIGHT FOR VICTORY&lt;/b&gt; Directly control the path of any ship on the battlefield or give commands to the entire fleet through the Cosmic Controller. Playing a game takes only seconds to learn, and advanced players can spend hours creating the perfect strategy..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/979520/Starblazer/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Starship Commander: Arcade&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Oq3dnkY4XWg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;STARSHIP COMMANDER&lt;/b&gt; is a seated experience that lasts 10-20 minutes, has replayability based off what you say, requires you to speak English, and is comfortable for new and experienced VR players alike. Non VR-Players will need a combo headphone/headset microphone and a mouse for an optimal experience. &lt;br /&gt;

The Arcade Experience finally comes home! Starship Commander: Arcade is a cinematic, choose-your-own-adventure narrative, inspired by classic PC adventure games like Day of the Tentacle and Telltale's Walking Dead series. Go faster-than-light on an adventure through space, as you infiltrate an alien spy facility on a top-secret mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/598400/Starship_Commander_Arcade/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Bullet Roulette VR&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/aEucJE18W24&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bullet Roulette VR&lt;/b&gt; is a casual game for four players. Each player randomly become one of 6 characters. Before shooting you should draw 2 cards that can completely change the rules of the game. If the player survives, he will get $ 1 for which he can shoot another player on the next turn. If he killed another player, then he takes his money. An unsuccessful attempt to shoot another player takes all the money. Be cold blooded and cunning to win! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1103880/Bullet_Roulette_VR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Playing God&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;!-- &lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TX58AbJq-xo&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Playing God is an interactive VR thought experiment that lets you imagine you are the captain of a space station, suddenly presented with a humanitarian crisis. It challenges its audience with a series of scenarios and questions based upon the narrative allowing the audience to explore how they would deal with a humanitarian crisis themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1358930/Playing_God/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;YUR&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0wj2L9Pa7Kg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
YUR provides calorie estimates for all VR games by using patent-pending technology to estimate calories burned across any VR game or experience.
  &lt;b&gt;YUR FEATURES:&lt;/b&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Realtime activity overlay over any game&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Estimated Heart Rate (Using Machine Learning)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Leveling and XP system where 1 kCal = 1 XP&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Support for dedicated Bluetooth Heart Rate monitors (optional)
    &lt;li&gt;Fitness Metrics (Squats, more coming soon)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dashboard with fitness tracking and historical achievements&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Leaderboard and Gameplay across VR games and much more&lt;/li&gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1188920/YUR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Snapshot VR&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OPv-jJk9psI&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Snapshot&lt;/b&gt; is a VR arena shooter built for e-sports with competitive solo and team play. Inspired by the real-life sport, Snapshot feels like playing paintball in the future. One shot, one kill. In competitive teams of up to 5, communication and coordination are the keys to victory.
  &lt;b&gt;Features:&lt;/b&gt;
 &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Room Browsing / Basic Matchmaking&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Cross-platform profiles with tracked stats and leaderboards&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Avatar Customization w/ Cosmetics&lt;/li&gt;
   &lt;li&gt;Third-party Map Editor w/ 50+ community maps playable&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Training maps with stationary and moving targets&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Multiple Locomotion Modes to accommodate any type of VR player&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1133580/Snapshot_VR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">If you are an avid gamer playing the latest vr games every other day, this article is compiled just for you. In this article, we filter through the many game titles available on steam, HTC Vive, oculus quest etc to provide you with the top picks for septemer 2020.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Best VR Movies you can Watch right now - Top Picks for 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-vr-movies-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Best VR Movies you can Watch right now - Top Picks for 2020" /><published>2020-09-10T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best%20vr%20movies%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-vr-movies-2020/">&lt;p&gt;Virtual reality is a sensation no doubt, it has been this way for gamers since a few years back. An industry adopting VR at an increasingly fast pace is the Movie Industry. Who can tell why? Well Movies are Immersive by them selves, Virtual Reality Movies are extra immersive. I will watch them at all cost, would you?. In this post, we share the top trending Vr movies you can get the best experience from - Just.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have written a few articles about &lt;a href=&quot;https://cheloverboard.netlify.app/top-10-room-scale-vr-game-to-play-in-2020/&quot;&gt;Vr games&lt;/a&gt; and how absolutely exciting they are, but I felt like the fun was not dispersed enough to all yet. Movies are amazing content, you can watch them by yourself, the whole family can see it together, or even in a thether by an whole audience of people. Virtual reality movies is a way of bringing people into the physical environment of the movies themselves. In our story, we share with you top picks of the best VR Movies in 2020:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Top Virtual Reality Movies for 2020&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;The Line&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10869836/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDRlYWY5YzQtMTc1Yi00Yzk1LTllNmEtMmY1NzliYmE0Y2Q0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQyMTYyNjQ@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Summary&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pedro and Rosa, two miniature dolls who are perfect for each other, find themselves reluctant to break boundaries to overcome limitations and live out their love story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10869836/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;Imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Alteration&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt6682676/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmI0MDdhNjgtMDhlMy00ZDk5LTlkMTctNGVlNWZjY2YyMjU2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEyNTYyMzU@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Summary:&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexandro volunteers for an experiment on the study of dreams. He doesn’t know that he will suffer Elsa’s intrusion, an A.I who will feed off his subconscious by digitalizing and dematerializing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt6682676/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;Imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Transformers: Autobots Alliance&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt7781226/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTRhMmY4OWQtNWQ2Zi00YzYwLTk2YjctOTIwNTk4ZmFmMWFhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNDYwMTE@._V1_UY268_CR3,0,182,268_AL_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Summary: &lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Autobots Alliance was formed on Earth by Optimus Prime and his Autobots to protect the human race from the Decepticons. Through discovery, interactive training and visual education, the Alliance provides humans with the skills and knowledge to recognize the signs of Decepticon infiltration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt7781226/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;Imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Gloomy Eyes&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9670896/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTUyNzI2MTU1N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjM5Nzc0NzM@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Summary: &lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the sun got tired of the humans it decided to hide and never rise again. The darkness awoke the dead from their graves. A zombie kid called Gloomy and a mortal girl called Nena fall in love and immerse in a deep connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9670896/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;Imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;The Limit&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt8011436/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2FmODM0ZTAtYWJjMC00OTNmLWJiMzUtM2NjYmNlN2JiMmI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzI3MzkxOTQ@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Summary: &lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a rogue agent with a mysterious past, you enlist the help of enhanced super-assassin M-13 (Michelle Rodriguez) to retrieve your identity and strike against the deadly organization that created you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt8011436/?ref_=kw_li_tt&quot;&gt;Imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it, the best Vr movie titles aorund at the moment. Following through with the links, you can observe that most of the movies are very short experience, this is as a result of motion sickness viewers are likely to have. In gaming, this is not a very big problem as in movie production because a gamer controls his/her movement most of the time and can adapt easily to the scene. In movies though, viewers are guided all the way and too much of this can cause motion sickness in some people. Thanks for reading through, I hope this list simplifies your work in searching for vr experiences to enjoy at this time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">Virtual reality is a sensation no doubt, it has been this way for gamers since a few years back. An industry adopting VR at an increasingly fast pace is the Movie Industry. Who can tell why? Well Movies are Immersive by them selves, Virtual Reality Movies are extra immersive. I will watch them at all cost, would you?. In this post, we share the top trending Vr movies you can get the best experience from - Just.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 Best Room-Scale VR Games to Play in 2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/top-10-room-scale-vr-game-to-play-in-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Best Room-Scale VR Games to Play in 2020" /><published>2020-09-07T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/top%2010%20room-scale%20vr%20game%20to%20play%20in%202020</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/top-10-room-scale-vr-game-to-play-in-2020/">&lt;p&gt;VR Games is the new trend for gamers all over the world. Just like regular games there exists a lot of types to choose from. Among these is Room-Scale VR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Room-Scale VR( Gentle Introduction)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cited from &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Room_scale&quot;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;: Room-scale is a design model for virtual reality (VR) experiences which allows users to freely walk around a play area, with their real-life motion reflected in the VR environment. Using 360 degree tracking equipment such as infrared sensors, the VR system monitors the user’s movement in all directions, and translates this into the virtual world in real-time. This allows the player to perform tasks, such as walking across a room and picking up a key from a table, using natural movements. In contrast, a stationary VR experience might have the player navigate across the room using a joystick or other input device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vive.com/eu/&quot;&gt;HTC Vive&lt;/a&gt; virtual-reality system incorporates room-scale tracking in its core design, using two infrared tracking stations located in opposite corners of the room to monitor the movement of the player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oculus.com/rift/&quot;&gt;Oculus Rift VR system&lt;/a&gt; was introduced primarily for front facing 180 degree experiences. However, Oculus now supports two sensor diagonal placement roomscale or users can purchase a third sensor to enable more robust room-scale tracking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a better understanding of room-sclae vr and how it differs from Stationary VR/ Seated VR, Browse through our list of Top best Room Scale VR Games in 2020 that you can derive best immersion and satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Hardware for VR Gaming&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our list of room-scale vr games covers the top new titles for the HTC Vive, Oculus Quest, Oculus Rift S (the successor to the Oculus Rift), PlayStation VR, Valve Index, and Windows Mixed Reality headsets. Many of these devices (and the games themselves) have gotten cheaper in the past couple of years, which makes them a more easily justifiable purchase.
Gamers using Headsets like the HTC Vive, Oculus Quest, Oculus Rift S, Valve Index and Windows Mixed Reality has to consider the hardware requirements for them. For the best experience use top-of-the-line-GPUs mounted on powerful gaming desktops or VR-ready laptops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;10+ Best Room-Scale VR Games to play in 2020&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Half-Life: Alyx&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TX58AbJq-xo&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Half-Life: Alyx is Valve’s VR return to the Half-Life series. It’s the story of an impossible fight against a vicious alien race known as the Combine, set between the events of Half-Life and Half-Life 2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playing as Alyx Vance, you are humanity’s only chance for survival. The Combine’s control of the planet since the Black Mesa incident has only strengthened as they corral the remaining population in cities. Among them are some of Earth’s greatest scientists: you and your father, Dr. Eli Vance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/546560/HalfLife_Alyx/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;BONEWORKS&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w8a1BAolFIk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BONEWORKS Is a narrative VR action adventure using advanced experimental physics mechanics. Dynamically navigate through environments, engage in physics heavy combat, and creatively approach puzzles with physics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Advanced Physics: Designed entirely for consistent universal rules, the advanced physics mechanics encourage players to confidently and creatively interact with the virtual world however you want.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Combat: Approach combat in any number of ways you can think of following the physical rules of the game’s universe. Melee weapons, firearms, physics traps, environments, can all be used to aid you in fights with enemy entities.
Weapons, lots of weapons: Boneworks provides players with a plethora of physics based weaponry; guns, swords, axes, clubs, spears, hammers, experimental energy weapons, nonsensical mystery tools, and anomalous physics weapons.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Interaction: Hyper realistic VR object and environment interaction.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Story: Play through the game’s mysterious narrative and explore the deep inner workings of the Monogon Industries’ artificial intelligence operating system; Myth OS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/823500/BONEWORKS/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;STRIDE&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/e9ToUaop_GM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;STRIDE is a parkour action game in virtual reality. Experience the feeling of vertigo as you stream between rooftops and flow across balconies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1292040/STRIDE/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Into the Radius VR&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hrgVXegmRPQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Into the Radius is a single-player survival shooter developed exclusively for premium Virtual Reality headsets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Players are sent stalking through the surreal post-apocalyptic Pechorsk Radius Zone where physics-based interaction, realistic weapon handling, and moody atmosphere will get your adrenaline pumping as you struggle to survive in an unforgiving dystopian environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open-world exploration, climbing, stealth and a dynamic day/night cycle. This creepy immersive VR survival shooter is inspired by ‘Roadside Picnic’. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Explore&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are miles and miles of forests, swamps and crumbling industrial ruins for you to explore however you want.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;But be careful: the Radius is filled with strange, lethal anomalies and hostile forces that threaten anyone foolish or daring enough to risk their lives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Orienteer with your realistic map, plan your mission route, climb over obstacles, scout out shelters, uncover loot caches, and try not to get killed. At least not too often.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Realistic Weapons&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Featuring classic Soviet firearms like the AKM Kalashnikov, PM Pistolet Makarova, SKS Carbine, and much more to come. Realistic interaction, manual magazine loading with different ammo types and weapon attachments.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be sure to switch off the safety before you start firing! Realistic bullet physics cause ricochets, and bullets can penetrate different kinds of materials.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take care of your weapons – if they take damage or their condition deteriorates, they will begin to jam.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1012790/Into_the_Radius_VR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;BattleGroupVR&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RcOiSp1RZ_s&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BattleGroupVR is a first-person real-time space strategy where you lead a fleet into battle from the bridge of your own flagship. As the battle group commander, you lead the charge as you are part of the action, not some armchair general who orders little units from above. You are part of the battle fighting alongside your chosen captains and warships. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unlock and acquire a variety of different types of ships&lt;/b&gt;, each with their own unique special abilities, characteristics, and weapon slots. From fast striking corvettes, long-range missile destroyers, electronic warfare science vessels, dangerous carriers, and powerful battleships. All are at your command. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Equip your vessels with the best weapons and technology&lt;/b&gt;. From heavy cannons, missile launchers, point defense lasers - a large selection of weapons and components are at your disposal. Arming your fleet with a wide array of capabilities to ensure your battlegroup is prepared for whatever challenges you encounter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1178780/BattleGroupVR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Karnage Chronicles&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/X8tZlbuzd70&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every five thousand years the planets align and create a rift in the fabric of cosmos. It’s prior to such an event that this story unfolds. Play as a Murkwraith, an undying knight barred from Death’s domain, and cursed to eternal servitude for sins committed eons ago. Experience a rich story that takes you on a perilous journey through dark dungeons filled with monsters, traps, puzzles, treasure and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Play alone or together with friends. Karnage Chronicles supports 1-4 players, with auto-scaling of monster strength and number of spawns as people come and go. Full drop-in / drop-out support allows you to play and have fun while waiting for friends or randoms to join your game, even allowing you to change party size on the fly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Karnage Chronicles is an action RPG designed from ground up to fully immerse you in the magic of VR.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose between several types of locomotion by accessing settings in-game.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take full advantage of an inventory system made specifically for VR.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unparalleled anti-wiggle system for close quarter combat. In this game you cannot tickle your enemies to death as the velocity of your swing defines the damage you do to your enemies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Customizable weapon presets allow for quick switching between weapons in combat, and there are quick slots for easy access to consumables like potions and food.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parry incoming attacks with your weapon or block them with a shield. Take full advantage of room-scale VR to dodge and sidestep arrows or magic hurled at you from afar. There are no random hit chances, all is player skill based, same goes for avoiding enemy attacks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/611160/Karnage_Chronicles/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Vertigo Remastered&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FgZhkS5sCA0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vertigo Remastered is a complete overhaul and occasional reimagining of the 2016 original, bringing modern VR gameplay, new content, and countless fixes/improvements to the table. Some of the best features and upgrades since Vertigo include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fully physics driven weapon handling and interaction system&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A huge catalog of new and returning enemies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hybrid teleport/smooth locomotion to support any comfort level&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unlockable upgrade tree&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Functional checkpoints&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Advanced spectator options - including experimental asymmetric co-op mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;It’s a classic premise&lt;/b&gt; - a massive subterranean scientific facility full of mysteries, with aliens bursting in from alternate universes to wreak havoc. The twist? You’re one of those aliens. But you’re not here to wreak havoc (collateral damage disregarded), you’re just trying to get home. A difficult endeavor, as it turns out this facility is more than prepared to deal with extraterrestrial threats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Explore the sprawling underground facilities of Planck Interdimensional’s Quantum Reactor&lt;/b&gt;, filled with dark secrets, adorable drones, and parallel universes. You find yourself in the bowels of this machine after being whisked away from your home, and, armed with only the tools you can find, you must make your way to the surface, and the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1318090/Vertigo_Remastered/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Swords of Gurrah&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nyUNYVRTiQE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fight in front of a blood thirsty crowd as a Sci-Fi Gladiator in Swords of Gurrah. Swords of Gurrah is a virtual reality game focused around hand-to-hand combat weapons. Fighters come from all over of their own free will to risk their lives against man or beast!!!! Fight to the death all to experience the thrill of victory - and if defeated to die for glory! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gurrah is a single player and multiplayer online game. It takes skill beyond typical gaming to keep up: swing, slice, slash, dodge, duck, and destroy. VR does amazing things to bring life-like hand-to-hand combat into your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Weapons;&lt;/b&gt;
These weapons are designed to shatter and regrow on every collision. This allows you to block and parry in a way previously never before seen in Virtual Reality due to the limitations of the technology. No longer will VR sword fighting feel clunky and inconsistent; the weapons are light weight, fluid but pack a punch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Beasts:&lt;/b&gt;
The arena presents many threats to keep gladiators on their toes. Fully armored bulls, tigers, hydras and more are ready for battle. Bred and bio-engineered to fight with ferocity. Each beast presents a new challenge, testing the ability of a warrior to adjust on the fly. The crowd must be entertained!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/833090/Swords_of_Gurrah/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;A-Tech Cybernetic VR&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5yJ7aHoiy4I&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A-Tech Cybernetic is a first-person shooter built from the ground up for VR. It features two separate game modes: a classic swarm mode to put your shooting and survival skills to the test and a story mode that takes you to a futuristic biomedical company overrun by mutants. Control everything with real-life movements, interact with your surroundings as if they were actually there, experience a new kind of gameplay that’s more immersive than ever before, thanks to VR. Be the badass guy you always wanted to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/578210/ATech_Cybernetic_VR/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;Tales Of Glory&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/D6jRgABS_is&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don your VR helm, choose your weapons, and command your troops to victory while you immerse yourself in the fury and excitement of this medieval battle simulator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will you be defeated? Or with the blood of your enemies, will you write your own Tales of Glory?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;A NEW STANDARD FOR MEDIEVAL MELEE FIGHTS:&lt;/b&gt;
Tales Of Glory is setting a new standard for medieval melee fights, bringing best of both worlds by combining large scale battles and full physics one vs many combat, everything packed into a 30+ hours sandbox campaign&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMMERSION AND ENDLESS POSSIBILITIES:&lt;/b&gt;
Participate in huge battles on 40 beautifully created battlefields. Raid the coast, defend you castle, infiltrate places, attack convoys and defeat your enemies, again and again.
The game’s randomization system allows you to get a different fight every time you start the level and realistic physics + ragdolling ensure an overwhelming fighting experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WAR OF THE FIVE CAMPAIGN:&lt;/b&gt;
Create your own story as you fight your way against the 5 kingdoms to avenge the slaughter of your family.
Recruit your army, gain skills, manage your realm, manipulate lords &amp;amp; kings through diplomacy, lay waste to your enemies’ strongholds &amp;amp; villages, participate in tournaments &amp;amp; missions to gain fame, visit the local shops to buy new gear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/636970/Tales_Of_Glory/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;font-weight: 600;&quot;&gt;WAR DUST - 32 vs 32 Battles&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0z-JVVHKAgk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Large-scale tactical warfare in Virtual Reality&lt;/b&gt;
With War Dust, we want to push the boundaries of Virtual Reality and create epic battles on a scale that has never been reached before.A total immersion experience that throws you into a breathtaking action film, full of explosions and dynamic tactics. The opportunity to live an incredible situation where armies clash.
Our goal is to create a feeling of being a part of a real epic war, not just a small combat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;64 PLAYERS&lt;/b&gt;
We have always wanted to create large-scale battles rather than small skirmishes which is why War Dust gives you the opportunity to join a company of 32 soldiers. With 64 fighters on the battlefield, War Dust will take you into the largest online battles that have ever been made in VR. Everyone has a role to play on the battlefield: one single man, at the right place at the right time, can make a decisive difference. Get ready to be this difference, to dare, to fight, and defeat your enemies.
Solidarity, rivalry, cooperation, confrontation: enjoy virtual reality from a new perspective. We look forward to share that experience with our players!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.steampowered.com/app/957790/WAR_DUST__32_vs_32_Battles/&quot;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt; (Valve Index, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift, Windows Mixed Reality)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings us to the end of the list. Among them, the best Room Scale VR games to play in 2020. This list is ranked based on positive reviews, graphics, game time length, physics and a few other designs. Spoiler, most games in the list have a price tag on them and if you are like me, you are probably thinking “aren’t there any top but &lt;b&gt;free&lt;/b&gt; Vr games around”?. Lucky for us, some developers open their games for everyone to play for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;What about Free Room-Scale Games?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The number of titles available for free room-scale vr currently pales in comparison to what you can find when you have some dollars to spend. That said, there are a few titles worth checking out:&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">VR Games is the new trend for gamers all over the world. Just like regular games there exists a lot of types to choose from. Among these is Room-Scale VR</summary></entry></feed>