<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-23T11:49:28+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ChelOverboard</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">My Reaper Girlfriend MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-reaper-girlfriend-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Reaper Girlfriend MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20reaper%20girlfriend%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-reaper-girlfriend-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;You were living a normal life as a student, but on the way home from school one day, you see the girl you have a crush on about to be hit by a car! [..]

You jump in and manage to save her just in time… But unfortunately, you take the hit! You wake up to find that your soul has left your body and two grim reapers, who happen to be very cute girls, show up to take you to the afterlife. Knowing that you saved your crush’s life, you’re okay with moving on… However, the reapers are impressed by your sacrifice and decide to bring you back under one condition: You become their assistant reaper!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

You agree to their proposal and wake up in bed back home, thinking it was all a dream. But when the two reapers show up asking you to report for duty, you quickly realize you might of bit off more than you can chew… Will you be able to help them with their mission to collect souls? Will you be able to find out why two cute girls like them became grim reapers? Will your crush discover your secret?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Find out in My Reaper Girlfriend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

❏Characters❏&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Marie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This reaper is what you’d call a tsundere. She’s tough on you at first, but eventually, she begins to open up to you. However, you learn that she wasn’t always a reaper… Will you be able to unlock the secrets of her heart?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Elsa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Elsa is Marie's boss and takes her duties as a reaper very seriously. Getting along with her proves difficult, but maybe if you can prove your abilities as an assistant, she’ll be a little nicer...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Mika&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Your crush and also your classmate, Mika seems like your average high school girl. But it turns out, she has a tendency to find herself in life-threatening situations. It seems there’s something supernatural going on… But will she find out about your new job?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">You were living a normal life as a student, but on the way home from school one day, you see the girl you have a crush on about to be hit by a car! [..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mystery of the Murderous Dream MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mystery-of-the-murderous-dream-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mystery of the Murderous Dream MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mystery%20of%20the%20murderous%20dream%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mystery-of-the-murderous-dream-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;A series of unfortunate events has forced you to move back to the countryside where you spent your childhood. Sadly, you don’t have many memories of the time you spent there! [..]

Things aren’t all bad, though - Chinatsu and Chifuyu, two adorable sisters at your new school are glad to have you! However, Chinatsu mentions an urban legend of “Ichika’s Mansion,” a supposedly cursed old mansion at the edge of town. You don’t think too much about it, but on the bus home, you have a terrifying dream…
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

You’re still on the bus… but each of the passengers is labeled with a way of dying and when the bus stops, the first passenger in line is murdered in the way their label states! You wake up thinking it was just a dream, but you hear news of a boy in your school being murdered last night. You take a look at a photo of him and… It’s the boy that was murdered in your dream! It doesn’t take long to realize that this isn’t just a nightmare. Every time you ride the bus, another passenger is murdered and your turn is coming up soon!.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Chinatsu and Chifuyu, along with their older sister, Chiharu, explain to you that this is all part of Ichika’s Curse. Anyone who enters the mansion will be cursed by her spirit. But how could you be cursed if you’ve never been to the mansion? It seems Chiharu knows more about your past that she’s willing to disclose...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Will you be able to stop the curse before it’s your turn? Will you be able to unlock the secrets of your past? Will you discover who Ichika truly is?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

❏Characters❏&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Chinatsu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Energetic and friendly, Chinatsu is a fan of all things supernatural. She’s the one that first lets you know of the curse and is eager to seek out the truth. She tends to act before she thinks, but will she fall victim to the curse as well…?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Chifuyu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Chifuyu is Chinatsu’s twin sister and is a little more closed off than her. She’s not a fan of the occult, but tags along anyway because she loves her sister. Will you be able to protect her from becoming another passenger of the cursed bus?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Chiharu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This mature senpai is Chinatsu and Chifuyu’s older sister and though you don’t remember, she seems to know who you are. She seems determined to solve the mystery of Ichika’s curse, but what could be her motivation…?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">A series of unfortunate events has forced you to move back to the countryside where you spent your childhood. Sadly, you don’t have many memories of the time you spent there! [..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Phantom Hearts MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/phantom-hearts-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Phantom Hearts MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/phantom%20hearts%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/phantom-hearts-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;Your parents are set to move to Japan, but you decide return to your hometown on your own after ten years of being away[..]

Some parts of the town have changed; some have not. Ten years ago, you left behind your crying and heartbroken best friend. What will happen when you reunite?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

The school that you have enrolled in seems normal in the beginning. Two sisters quickly befriend you – one who is spirited and brave and the other who is calm and shy. They let you in on a little secret: not everything in the school is as it seems. The peaceful facade at school is simply hiding the scars and horrors underneath. A tragedy occurred in the school not long ago, and it seems that you have landed in the thick of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

ou are reunited with your childhood friend who has grown into a beautiful girl. This happiness does not last long, though. An innocent excursion to an abandoned school building quickly turns into a living nightmare due to your actions. With bodies piling up and rumors of ghosts haunting the hallways, what can you do to help your school and save your friends? The three beauties might be able to help, but will you have the power to make sure that you all make it out alive…?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

❏Characters❏&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Chloe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“I wasn’t sure you’d remember me, but I’m glad you do. I really missed you…”

Chloe is your childhood friend whom you haven’t seen for a number of years. She has been lonely since you left, but now that you are back, she’s hoping to reconnect. She’s usually sweet, but you are the only one who manages to bring out a myriad of emotions from her. Will you discover what lies deep within her heart?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Rita&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“I’ve seen things, and so will you now that you’re here. I will protect my sister and this school no matter what.”

Rita is the vibrant and passionate girl who befriends you on your first day. She is Anna’s older sister and always does her best to protect her loved ones. She is very brave and follows you into whatever adventure or mystery you find. Will you be able to keep her safe from her own reckless behavior?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Anna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“I’ll be honest… I’m terrified, but I’m more scared of being alone than I am of helping to find out what is going on.”

Anna is Rita’s younger sister and is a shy and gentle soul. She is often terrified in the face of danger, but she does her best to try and help you solve the mystery surrounding the school. With your help, she might find more confidence. Will you help her to realize that she is brave for facing her fears?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">Your parents are set to move to Japan, but you decide return to your hometown on your own after ten years of being away[..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Initialize an Old Jekyll Site on a new Machine for Local Development</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/setting-up-an-old-jekyll-site-on-a-new-machine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Initialize an Old Jekyll Site on a new Machine for Local Development" /><published>2020-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/setting%20up%20an%20old%20jekyll%20site%20on%20a%20new%20machine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/setting-up-an-old-jekyll-site-on-a-new-machine/">&lt;p&gt;I currently use jekyll for two of my websites becasue it has a simple to learn interface and you can write less code using templates. I assume you have a blog built with jekyll that’s why you are probably reading this content now. Accoding to the title of this post, you would learn by the end how to set up your jekyll site on a new machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me explain better, so you can decide if this is the exact problem you might be facing. You sometime built your website using jekyll and perhaps it was hosted on github pages or using netlify, all in all, you have a github repo where you store your site files and which can be easily cloned. So, after building your site, maybe you want to set it up on a new machine for local production or you lost your last folder with your site contents and want to clone, pull, build a new one. If this is the problem you are facing, then you are on the right blog. I would show you a few possible mistakes you might be making if you are getting some errors and finally how to do this the right way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had this issue, I got a new PC and wanted to &lt;em&gt;git clone&lt;/em&gt; my &lt;em&gt;&lt;b&gt;old&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/em&gt; jekyll site on it so I could continue developing locally with &lt;em&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/em&gt; command before pushing for production. It took me about 5 days to figure it out, I was getting some errors I could not debug and almost all jekyll tutorials I could find online were on &lt;b&gt;How to set up a new jekyll site&lt;/b&gt;. Setting up a new jekyll site is pretty easy, you just need onle command, but that wasn’t what I was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Now here are a few things I tried:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I tried using the git clone command to clone my repo in a new folder, but when you try to access jekyll commands like &lt;b&gt;bundle exec jekyll serve&lt;/b&gt; to serve the files locally at “http://127.0.0.1:4000/”, you get the error of “jekyll is not installed or not a command”. This is because you are only cloning the repo and not installing jekyll in that directory. Well, if you try to install jekyll, bundler and dependencies in that folder with command &lt;b&gt;jekyll new PATH&lt;/b&gt;, you get an error of how the folder you are tryiong to instrall jekyll in already has some content and must be overwritten to proceed. But of course we don’t want that. So this was a process that did not work for me&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I tried first building a new jekyll site with the jekyll new command and later cloning my repo in that folder, but I was stumped when it actually cloned normally but as a sub-directory. I defineitely didn’t want that because now I have to move into that folder which still does not have jekyll installed. take a look at the image to understand better.
 &lt;img src=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it did take some time, tweaking some values to see if I could get it to work but finally this is what worked for me. If you have the same issue the steps below are simple and straight-forward to implement. It shhould take nothing more than 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Setting up Old Jekyll site for Local Development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;clear: both;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Step 1: Create a new Folder to Store Local Files&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you have to do is create a new directory where you want to host your files :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0;&quot;&gt;
mkdir SITE-FOLDER-NAME
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2: Install Jekyll Using Bundler&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note&lt;/b&gt;: Here it is assumed that you already have &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bundler&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Ruby + DevKit&lt;/a&gt;. If you don’t, refer to this article to set it up on your machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next you can use the &lt;em&gt;&lt;b&gt;jekyll new SITE-FOLDER-NAME&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/em&gt; command to build a fresh jekyll site with all the necessary gems and dependencies installed then change directory to that folder:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0;&quot;&gt;
new jekyll SITE-FOLDER-NAME
cd SITE-FOLDER-NAME
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Step 3: Create a local repository for your Jekyll site&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; Here you must have &lt;b&gt;Git for Windows&lt;/b&gt; installed and added to PATH Variables to use the “git” command. You can install Git in the official website for Windows &lt;a href=&quot;https://git-scm.com/download/win&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a simple jekyll site generated, you can use jekyll serve command to load it at a localhost and all that. The next thing to do is to initialize an empty repository in that folder which we would be pushing to later, you can do it with this simple command:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0;&quot;&gt;
git init
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Step 4: Download Repository as a Zip file and Extract&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, about your site’s files, what I tried that worked well is to download it directly instead of cloning. You can download all your files as a zip from ur repo’s page. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets\images\Blog\download-repo-as-zip.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this, go ahead and extract it directly into the folder where jekyll has been installed. Now you likely have some specific files which would be duplicated going into the folder like “Gemfile” “Gemfile.lock” “config.yml” etc, in this case you should replace the new files for the exsiting ones. Now run “bundle exec jekyll serve” command and you should see your site built like before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Step 5: Stage, Commit and Push&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next thing to do is to run this commands:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0;&quot;&gt;
	git add .
	git commit -m &quot;Commit Message here&quot;
	git push -u origin master
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might face a prompt asking you for some credentials for identity like username and email. Simply type them in. You would also need to log into your repo afresh, this way the empty repo initialized in that folder knows where the commit should be pushed to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Alternate Way&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from downloading your repo as a zip and extracting it into jekyll site’s folder you can run this command to connect your remote repository on Github:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot;&gt;
	git remote add origin https://github.com/username-or-organization-name/your-remote-repository-name
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;clear: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a process that worked for me and it can be completed in as little as 30 minutes by following the guide. Thanks for reading this material. I hope this guide can help give the solutions you might have been searching for. If you are not clear on some parts, or need further directions please leave a message below in the comments section. I would be glad to see how I can be of help.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chel</name></author><summary type="html">I currently use jekyll for two of my websites becasue it has a simple to learn interface and you can write less code using templates. I assume you have a blog built with jekyll that’s why you are probably reading this content now. Accoding to the title of this post, you would learn by the end how to set up your jekyll site on a new machine.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Angel Girlfriend MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-angel-girlfriend-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Angel Girlfriend MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-07-11T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20angel%20girlfriend%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-angel-girlfriend-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;You’re just a typical high school student. You’ve got good friends. You’ve got good grades. Everything in your life is going well[..]

But you can’t help but feel empty. Surely there’s got to be more to life than this? If you only had a sign! Well, your prayers are answered when you encounter a stunning girl mysteriously standing in the middle of the street. She tells you that she’s looking for an angel… You immediately realize that this girl is delusional and that this isn’t the kind of change you were looking for in your life. You head home. So much for that..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Suddenly, you hear someone tapping on your window. It’s that girl from before… But HOLY COW! She’s got beautiful angel wings and is flying outside your window! She’s actually a real angel! Now that she’s got your attention, she explains that she needs help finding her sister, a fallen angel. Not having a clue as to what on earth or heaven is going on, you agree to let her stay with you, only to wake up the next morning to find yet another gorgeous angel in your room. If there is a God, he must really like you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Before you know it, the two angel girls have joined your school, and you’re helping them look for this ”fallen angel.” But, you soon learn that angels aren’t the only unearthly beings hiding in your school. Powerful devils looking to cause trouble are lurking about too! Can you help these two angel beauties save this fallen angel and foil the devils’ plot before all hell breaks loose? Don’t wait for a sign from heaven. Find out in My Angel Girlfriend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

❏Characters❏&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Mai&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Mai is the first angel you encounter. She’s cute and well-meaning but has a lot to learn when it comes to normal human behavior. This can lead to some “interesting” situations. She cares deeply for her sister Meg, an angel banished to earth. She’ll stop at nothing to bring her home, but is that Meg really wants?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Reina&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Reina comes to earth to help Mai find Meg. Apparently Mai said it was okay for Reina to stay at your house. Well, at least, she is more familiar with human customs. Reina is an intelligent peacemaker with a playful side. Not only can she diffuse any situation with her words, but she can also use her AESP (Angelic Extrasensory Perception) to turn things in her favor. Will her powers be enough to take on the devils in the school?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Meg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Meg is Mai’s sister. She’s stubborn but kindhearted. Desiring to help humanity, she was banished from the angelic realm by the Archangel for meddling in earthly affairs. Meg has grown accustomed to life on earth, having grown bored of the strict lifestyle back home anyway. She doesn’t seem thrilled to hear that Mai wants to take her back to Heaven. But will the Archangel actually let her come back?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">You’re just a typical high school student. You’ve got good friends. You’ve got good grades. Everything in your life is going well[..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Otaku Like me has 2 Fiancees MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/otaku-like-me-has-2-fiancees-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Otaku Like me has 2 Fiancees MOD APK 1.0.0 (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-06-28T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/otaku-like-me-has-2-fiancees-mod-apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/otaku-like-me-has-2-fiancees-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;Hiding your identity as an otaku has always been part of your life. But that hasn’t stopped you from having an enjoyable, average life in high school. One day, you find yourself [..]

meeting up with a beautiful senpai who is also the president of the club you belong to. It seems she has a favor to ask of you. Nothing big. You know, just… pretend to be her lover to avoid getting out of an arranged marriage?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

You decide to help her out, but before you have time to process the whole thing, your energetic classmate seems to want to “talk” to you about something. You go along with her only to discover that she’s found out about your secret identity as an otaku! Luckily, it turns out she’s an otaku as well, but it seems she has a favor to ask of you as well and if you don’t cooperate, the whole school finds out about your “hobbies.” Now, what might that favor be? You guessed it… Act as her lover to get out of an arranged marriage!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Just yesterday, you thought this could only happen in your favorite anime… Now you have to figure out how to survive what might be the most challenging situation any protagonist has ever faced! Can two fake relationships ever turn into a single real one? Find out in An Otaku like me has 2 Fiancees?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

☆Characters☆&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Mizuki◇&lt;br /&gt;
Mizuki is an energetic classmate of yours and also an otaku just like you! She enjoys nothing more than cosplay and lolita fashion, but she’s actually from an extremely rich family that wants her to get married to help their business. Will your shared love of all things anime turn your fake relationship into the real deal?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Tsubame◇&lt;br /&gt;
Tsubame is the president of the tea ceremony club at your school and is your favorite senpai. With long black hair and a traditional upbringing, she defines classiness! However, she’s lived a sheltered life and is in search of new experiences… Could you and your otaku ways turn out to be what she truly desires?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Himawari◇&lt;br /&gt;
Himawari is Tsubame’s younger sister and can be quite a handful! Tsundere would be the word that you’d use to describe her, but to most, she’s a rising star on the basketball team. It seems the only thing connecting the two of you is her sister, but you soon learn that there’s a lot more to this girl… What could her secret be?
…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">Hiding your identity as an otaku has always been part of your life. But that hasn’t stopped you from having an enjoyable, average life in high school. One day, you find yourself [..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My High School Detective MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-high-school-detective-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My High School Detective MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20high%20school%20detective%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-high-school-detective-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;You’re back in school after the long break, and as the smartest guy in the class, you’re confident it’s gonna[..]

be another boring semester without any real challenges. Well, you can throw that idea out the window! Two rival detective girls transfer to your school and it seems a phantom thief has followed them too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

You try to stay away at first, but somehow you end up getting involved with both the detective girls and the phantom thief. Looks like it’s time to say goodbye to your boring everyday routine! However, you soon come to enjoy being a detective and discover that there are plenty of mysteries worth solving at your school. The fact that your fellow detective friends are cute girls definitely doesn’t hurt either!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Will you be able to solve all of the mysteries? Find out in My High School Detective!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

☆Characters☆&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Maya◇&lt;br /&gt;
Maya just transferred to your school this semester and used to run a detective club at her old school. Her intellect is unmatched, but she can be a little “off” every once in a while and is quickly brought to tears.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Izumi◇&lt;br /&gt;
This detective girl claims to be Maya’s rival and can be a little prickly at times. She’s not quite as sharp as Maya, but she makes up for it with her energetic and proactive personality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇Olivia◇&lt;br /&gt;
Timid would be how a lot of people describe Olivia. But once you get to know her, you realize she’s a little…. eccentric. Like, dresses up as a phantom thief to try to befriend people eccentric…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">You’re back in school after the long break, and as the smartest guy in the class, you’re confident it’s gonna[..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Wolf Girlfriend MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-wolf-girlfriend-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Wolf Girlfriend MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-05-24T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-24T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20wolf%20girlfriend%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-wolf-girlfriend-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;Your life as a high school student has been going pretty smoothly so far. You and your childhood friend Mariya have been[..]

making the best of it, until one day, you hear about two strange creatures escaping from a lab. You think nothing too much of it until one day, you come across two mysterious girls on your way home from school one day that clearly seemed distressed. Being the good samaritan you are, you decide to take them home and give them something to eat and you learn that their names are Maki and Ayano.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
But later that night when moonlight shines through the windows, they suddenly transform revealing that they are wolf girls! It’s that moment you realize that they are the creatures that escaped from the lab! In the heat of things, Mariya gets bit by one of them and she starts turning into a wolf girl… Will you be able to solve the mystery of the wolf girls and help your childhood friend!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Find out in My Wolf Girlfriend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

☆Characters☆&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

◇ Maki ◇&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This wolf girl tends to act before she thinks, but she’s a caring individual at heart. She’s a little afraid of regular humans and has a fear of loud noises because of her time at the lab. Will you be able to help her overcome her trauma?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

❏ Ayano ❏&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
She’s been friends with Maki forever and is the more down to earth of the two. Her cool demeanor can make her seem a little terse at times. However, she’s deeply loyal and feels indebted towards Maki. What mysteries could her past hold?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

○ Mariya ○&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
She’s been your friend since you were little kids and is the nicest person you know. She’s accidentally bitten by Maki and becomes a wolf girl herself, but will you be able to help her adjust to this new reality?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">Your life as a high school student has been going pretty smoothly so far. You and your childhood friend Mariya have been[..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Elemental Girlfriend MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-elemental-girlfriend-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Elemental Girlfriend MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-05-14T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20elemental%20girlfriend%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-elemental-girlfriend-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;Life’s never easy being the underdog at school. You’ve learned to cope, but on the way home from school one day, it looks like a reckless[..]

driver speeding towards you is about to bring it all to an end! When you open your eyes, you find… Three cute spirit girls?! Each one of them represents an element and apparently they’ve been forced out of their world until they can collect special stones which they need YOUR help for!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You agree to this thinking it must all be a dream… But then you wake up, all three of them are there! Will spirits of fire, water and earth help to spice up your boring life, or are you about to experience the biggest roller coaster ride of your life?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Find out in My Elemental Girlfriend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

☆Characters☆&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Laman the Fire Spirit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Energetic and always enthusiastic, this fire spirit has a tendency to act before she thinks. She’s been labeled a drop out because she can’t control her massive powers and she feels a sense of inferiority because of this. Will you be the one to help her realize her potential?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Udie the Water Spirit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Though she can be a little callous at times, Udie is a caring spirit at heart that has trouble expressing her true feelings. She seems fully competent, but she holds a secret as to why she is with the other two dropouts. Will you be able to discover the secrets of her heart?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Canon the Earth Spirit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Canon is meek and reserved but has a heart of gold. She’s always had trouble controlling her powers and Udie has acted like a big sister to her. She wants desperately to overcome her weaknesses, but will you be able to help her do so?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">Life’s never easy being the underdog at school. You’ve learned to cope, but on the way home from school one day, it looks like a reckless[..]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Animal School Romance MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-animal-school-romance-mod-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Animal School Romance MOD APK Latest (Free Premium Choices)" /><published>2020-05-10T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my%20animal%20school%20romance%20mod%20apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-animal-school-romance-mod-apk/">&lt;p&gt;When scientists found a way to anthropomorphize animals, the world changed forever.Now dubbed “anthros,” these[..]

new creations live alongside humans—but a strict caste system keeps the two groups apart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You’ve always been sympathetic toward anthros and believe they deserve equal rights, but you’re afraid to speak out against popular opinion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

That changes when one of your anthro classmates tries to kill herself because of the way people treat her. Something has to change, both for her and for the anthro community overall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

With the help of your best friend and an enthusiastic classmate, you vow to help her build more self-confidence… and maybe change the way society views anthros along the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Characters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

* [Shy Anthro] Christa
Lacking confidence because she’s an anthro, Christa prefers to stay out of the public eye, but she isn’t happy with her life. Can you help her emerge from her shell and prove herself to the world?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

* [Best Friend] Zoe
Popular and outgoing, Zoe has been your best friend ever since you were children. What most people don’t know is that she’s an anthro passing as human—a secret the two of you carefully guard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

* [Activist] Katie
Although human, Katie is an anthro rights activist with fierce ambitions and unwavering determination. You and Christa are the perfect candidates to help her with her latest crusade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
By making choices throughout the story, you’ll get to know your three classmates and see how the caste system has affected them. And as you fight together to change the way humans and anthros interact, you might also find true love…
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>chel</name></author><summary type="html">When scientists found a way to anthropomorphize animals, the world changed forever.Now dubbed “anthros,” these[..]</summary></entry></feed>